Someone one one
Someone one else
one one! someone one!
Yay!
Dareka ga suki da
I'm in love with someone
Anata mo suki da
I'm in love with you too
Motto gyutto kyori wo
So let's try and
Umetemiyou yo
Get a lot more closer
Hataraku no ga suki da
Working is my passion
Saboru no wa koi da
Skipping it is my hobby
Etto potto kokode
Can we... uh... *blush*
Sugoshite itai yo
Spend some time right here?
Haruka touku ni Utopia ga mieru yo
Over the distance I see a utopia
Kimi no hitomi no onsen ni hairoo!
Gonna take a dip inside the hot spring in your eyes!
Tamashii goon to chaimu wo utareta nara
When someone rings the chimes of your soul
Utarechattara
When they're rung
Ubuge fuwafuwa doriimu naderareta nara
When someone rubs a dream against the fluffy hairs of your skin
one one! someone one! one one!
Susume!
Move along!
Setsuna sa horori no mannaka inukaretara
When someone shoots you emotionally right on the mark
Inukarechattara
When you're shot
Kurubushi Guriguri hone ga kanjiteru nara
When someone knocks against the bones of your ankles and you feel it
Ase wo kakimashou!
Let's break some sweat!
one one! someone one
Yay!