Uh, I’ll have the Hamburger Special.
I’ll have the mixed fries.
Will that be all?
Yes.
Very well. Please wait just a moment.
Excuse me!
Oh, yes?
Who on earth is that?
Huh? What do you mean, who?
It’s Inami-chan, of course.
Inami-san.
Huh? What is it?
You serve female customers perfectly, right?
Huh? What is this all of a sudden?
Nothing. I think it’s amazing.
Could it be that... you like girls?
Hey, Katanashi-kun!
That’s... That’s not the case.
Usually... with men...
You mean hitting on men.
I keep telling you I hate men—
Wait, what?!
Well, I was thinking it would be great if we found a way for you to treat male customers like that too.
By the way, since you hit men, would you hit a little boy too?
A senior citizen?
I-I’d just try not to get too close to them.
What about cross-dressing men?
Cross-dressing women?
Shut up and stop asking me difficult questions!
I-I don’t know how to explain it. It’s just instinct!
Inami-chan...
Instinct? Oh man.
I’ve been told that guys are scary ever since I was little, so it’s just become a part of me.
What about your family—like your dad?
My dad got transferred away from home and never came back.
Must be out of self-defense.
But lately you’ve been able to speak easily with Katanashi-kun, right?
Really? My hard work must be paying off.
Although I’m the one bleeding for it...
I’ll try really hard to fix my androphobia, so...
Takanashi-kun, somehow, you seem different from other men...
You’re easy to hit, too!
Inami-san, androphobia is different
from just wanting to hit men, you know.
What’s wrong?
Actually, someone has been on my mind a lot lately.
I lose sleep at night thinking about her.
A girl? Does this mean it’s love?
Is it love, Katanashi-kun?
No, it’s not like that.
Doesn’t the Chief, Yachiyo-san, spark your interest?
Yachiyo-san, huh? I guess she does.
Right?
She’s pretty, nice, hard-working, and stylish; she doesn’t hit men, and she has boobs. I’m jealous.
No, I’m not talking about that. I
mean the katana she has at her waist.
Why does she carry that thing around?
Huh?
Now that you mention it...
Maybe she likes katanas?
Even if she likes them, she
can’t go carrying one around like that!
Don’t people usually carry weapons around?
No, they don’t!
Like a nail-bat.
You had one?
Hey, Yachiyo.
Yes, Kyouko-san?
I’m hungry.
Okay! Right away!
Kyouko-san, here you go!
Just as expected, Yachiyo—fast as ever.
This worries me.
That hit the spot.
You are quite welcome.
Takanashi, stop caring about trivial things and work, got it?
Kyouko-san, you’re so cool.
That person... Did she come here to eat parfaits instead of to work?
Guys.
Don’t use the restaurant’s food as you please.
But I have to take care of Kyouko-san.
Take care of the customers first.
Here. You guys too.
Okay.
Let’s go, Inami-chan!
S-Sure.
Satou-kun, if Kyouko-san comes, please don’t make parfaits for her, okay?
It’s my job to take care of her!
I won’t. Hurry up and go.
Thank you! I’ll be on my way.
You too. Hurry up and get out there.
Satou-san... There’s a normal person here!
Um... Would it be all right to ask you about the Chief?
Item 3
Yachiyo, Kyouko, Satou... And the returning Otoo-san.
Todoroki?
Yes. Can’t we do something about her?
It seems as though that katana is even scaring the customers.
Here is your cheeseburger set and fried ginger-pork special. Sorry for the wait.
The plate’s hot, so please be careful.
E-Excuse me...
Yes?
It’s nothing!
Would you like some coffee after your meal?
Y-Yes!
For some reason, the staff don’t
seem to mind, but it’s not normal!
Also, she makes too many parfaits for the manager.
Yeah...
But it’s pointless to even mention it.
Eh? Why is that?
Because, supposedly, she’s had
both of those problems since elementary school.
What?!
This is a story from about ten years ago.
For some reason, I used to get bullied
all the time when I was in elementary school.
Hey Todoroki! Carrying around a katana; are you stupid or something?
Stop it!
It’s dangerous.
And that’s when the ally of justice, Kyouko-san, appeared.
Glutton
Wh-What the...? What kind of outdated delinquent are you?!
You plan on interfering in a kids’ fight?
I’ll call the cops, you old hag!
Then, Kyouko-san took those bullies and...
Omission
Omission.
She did something we can’t even mention?!
Damn brats doing such childish things.
Ah, that was cool!
Huh?
Thank you very much for saving me.
More importantly...
I don’t have any money.
Don’t you have some bread from lunch or something?
Huh?
Are you getting bullied?
Y-Yes.
Hm...
All right, this must be some sort of fate.
I’ll beat everybody up for you...
so give me your leftover bread.
O-Okay!
K-Kyouko-san! If you’re hungry, I’ll go buy something!
It’s embarrassing that you’re being fed by a kid!
So lovely...
Since then, I’ve stayed by Kyouko-san’s side.
Chief, since when? And why are you doing your own flashback?!
Um, you may already know, but about your katana...
Oh, this? I’m embarrassed. Weird, isn’t it?
You see, my family runs a cutlery.
Ah, I see...?
We make everything from kitchen knives to katanas.
“It cuts well and stabs well.” That’s the Todoroki family motto.
Um... Chief, just because your family runs a cutlery
doesn’t mean you need to be carrying around a katana.
Well, you know, there are dangerous things in the world!
You’re the epitome of danger, Chief.
Yachiyo, I’m hungry!
Okay! I’ll be right there, Kyouko-san!
Well then, I’ll get back to work.
There you have it.
Oh, this is where you were.
We have a lot of orders piling up.
Can you return to work now, Satou-kun?
Right.
Be right there.
Satou-san, it must be nice to be so tall!
Want me to make you taller real fast?
Wow, really?!
See, you’re tall now.
Wait, don’t get mad, Taneshima.
If you get mad, your cells will die and you won’t grow taller.
Really?!
Haven’t you noticed that all tall people are calm? It’s because they haven’t wasted any cells.
I-I see!
So don’t get mad over little things.
Work hard, Taneshima-san.
Sure, I got it! Thanks, Satou-san! I’ll do my best!
Senpai...
Satou-kun, you really know how to handle Taneshima-san.
I guess so.
I wonder why you’re not so good at handling Todoroki-san, though.
Souma, I’ll bash your head in until you’re Taneshima-sized.
I’m kidding, I’m kidding.
Huh?
Thank you very much.
Whew, it’s finally over.
Katanashi-kun, good work today, as always!
You too, Senpai.
Now, all that’s left is to mop the floor—
Huh?
I’m tired of our restaurant’s food.
Obviously, since you eat so much of it.
Those who do not work do not eat.
Are you stupid, Takanashi? It’s because I don’t work that there’s nothing else to do but eat.
Then work.
Don’t worry, there’ll be some new food delivered soon.
Huh?
Eh?! Is he coming back?
Who is?
Our restaurant manager, the most important guy here.
More important than you?
That’s right.
Ah, then he must be lazier, more violent, and more arrogant than you. Is he old as well?
I’ll stab you.
I-It’s nothing to worry about! Otoo-san is a nice person!
Ah, excu—
I’m back.
Yay!
Senpai, he’ll eat you!
Oh, are you the new employee, Takanashi-kun?
Nice to meet you. I’m the restaurant manager, Otoo Hyougo.
Otoo Hyougo
Eh?!
Oh, sorry for scaring you. I
completely forgot I was wearing a mask.
N-No problem.
So this is the most important man in the restaurant?
More importantly, where did he come from, wearing that mask?
Great job taking care of things in my absence, Manager Shirafuji and Taneshima-san.
Oh, man. I suffered and suffered.
Really, I’m so sorry for causing so much trouble.
Huh? Isn’t the restaurant manager higher up than the manager?
It depends on the company, but here the
restaurant manager is hired by the company.
I take care of the business end, and I was the one to hire Manager Shirafuji.
Oh, so you’re a hired manager?
Had enough?
I’m not really around much. You can just think of me as a guy that comes around every so often.
Y-You don’t have to lower yourself that much.
Otoo-san! Where’s this mask from?
I’m not sure; I went to a lot of places.
Are you always on business trips when you’re not around?
Ah, like exploring different places in search of new foods?
No... I’m out looking for my missing wife.
What?
How’d it go, Otoo?
I couldn’t find her anywhere.
Not that.
Oh!
Here are the souvenirs.
Great work, Otoo.
Takanashi-kun, Taneshima-san,
if you’d like to, please help yourselves.
Th-Thank you.
She looks just like my wife.
The manager looks like your wife?
No, no. The wrapping paper.
When I find something that reminds me of my wife, I have to buy it.
So that’s why there are so many souvenirs.
This too?
Senpai, that’s going a little too far.
They look so similar.
Is your wife even human, then?
Oh, where has she gone? She should be somewhere in Japan.
Um, why did she go missing?
Well, you see, my wife is very bad with
directions. She got lost while shopping.
Eh?
So let me know if you see someone who looks like this.
Please call the cops.
How bad would you say your wife’s sense of direction is?
A long time ago, I once asked her which direction north was.
Up.
Up?
She said that the four directions were shown on the map, and north was up.
Wow! Is that right?
No; that's not right, senpai.
Takanashi, do you know where the whetstone is?
The whetstone?
No, I don’t know.
It should be in the kitchen.
Yeah, but it’s not there.
Did somebody from the floor take it?
Satou-kun, it’s dangerous to walk around with a knife.
There it is!
Woah, it’s shiny!
I’m worried.
It would be fine if she were just doing some maintenance, but...
Is it okay to sharpen a katana with a whetstone? Isn’t that bad?
Well, Satou-san, that’s not the problem here.
If you don’t take good care of your blade,
you’ll be in trouble when you actually need it.
It’d be trouble if she did use it!
There is someone I must cut down.
Oh, it’s just like a historical play!
Senpai, that’s not what’s going on.
Anyway, Chief, who are you going to cut down?
Satou-kun, Todoroki-san, it’s been a while.
My, welcome back from your long journey.
O-to-o-san.
To— Todoroki-san!
Ch-Chief! What are you doing?!
Hey, old man, did you do something to make her angry with you?
Rehearsing a historical play?
They ran.
Nothing! I haven’t done anything!
You betrayed me...
B-Betrayed? Me?
Yachiyo, is Otoo not back yet?
He’ll be back soon.
I see.
I hope he comes back soon...
...with souvenirs.
My dearest...
What? Your dearest what?!
I’m only able to make her parfaits.
And you... How could you bait her with food?!
Don’t give her things if you’re not serious about it!
What’s going to happen if she gets attached to you?!
T-Todoroki-san, please calm down.
Man, I’m tired of eating these souvenirs.
Yachiyo, I want a parfait.
Understood, Kyouko-san!
Kyouko-san, which would you like, strawberry or chocolate?
Hm. I’ll have both.
But you might hurt your stomach if you eat both.
It’s okay.
A-Are you okay?
W-Well, it’s not like she had any bad intentions.
But there was a thirst for blood.
Old man, you’re a nice guy.
No, well... It’s peaceful as long as she makes
parfaits for the manager, so I shouldn’t be in danger.
That’s true, but—
Otoo-san, have you met Inami-san?
Well, I know the name, but I’ve never met her.
It’d be nice if you could survive and find your wife.
Huh? Thank you...
Thank you very much.
Yachiyo.
Oh, Kyouko-san. Do you want a parfait?
Are you okay? You don’t seem too well.
Um... I’m feeling a bit under the weather.
I didn’t notice at all.
Kyouko-san is amazing.
If you’re not feeling well, go home.
Um, I’m okay.
Do you have a fever?
H-Hey.
A fever didn’t cause that.
Hey, get a hold of yourself, Yachiyo.
I made her rest, so she should be fine for now.
Isn’t she just overworked?
Huh?
Well, it’s just that it must be tough with the rest of the staff slacking off all the time.
And you don’t work.
Oh, I know! Kyouko-san, let’s teach you how to work!
It’ll be fun.
Work, huh?
You see, with plates, you hold them with
a towel so you don’t get any fingerprints on them.
L-Let’s try again.
Tips on not breaking them?
U-Um, it might be easier to learn something you like doing!
You can’t eat it! Kyouko-san!
What are you going to do, Senpai?
I thought about it, but isn’t it better if I don’t work? For everyone’s sake.
What?!
You know...
That way, you’ll think that “since the manager isn’t any good, we should do our best,” right?
So basically, not doing work is my work. I purposely don’t work.
Amazing.
Another twisted yet logical reason.
It’s okay. There’s no job that I can do!
That’s not true.
This is your job.
What is this?
It’s porridge.
And? You want me to eat this?
No, go take care of her.
Kyouko-san.
Satou went through the trouble of making you porridge.
No way... Just for me?
E-Eat it.
Kyouko-san.
Wow, it looks delicious.
Ah, it is.
G-Good for you.
Kyouko-san, please have some.
N-No, you eat it.
Well, it makes me feel better knowing that you’re eating well.
But you might catch my cold.
Actually, just get better by making me sick.
I learned after working today that
I’m no good without you by my side.
Hurry up and get better.
Yachiyo fainted.
A Few Days Later
I’m sorry for making you worry.
Thanks to you guys, I’m all better.
That’s great.
Now we can work together again.
Satou-kun, thank you for the porridge.
I’m glad you’re cured.
I’m hungry. Satou, make me something.
All right. You’re an employee, so 30% off.
You plan on taking money from me? I’m the manager.
Exactly. You’re the manager.
Don’t say that. Please make her something.
Todoroki-san’s first job after her
return is taking care of Kyouko-san.
Seems like it.
Satou-kun.
Look, Todoroki. If I made her something every time, we’d run out of ingredients.
And it’s busy right now. You have things to do too.
Things to do...?
I’ll start working in the kitchen so I can make food for Kyouko-san!
How far will you go?
Is it even okay for me to make food for her in the first place,
when you tried to cut down
old man Otoo for giving her souvenirs?
That’s because... I can trust Satou-kun.
Please make her some food, Satou-kun.
She’s going to die of starvation!
She won’t die. She’s had plenty.
Please, Satou-kun.
You’re going to make her something?
Only because she won’t work until the manager’s taken care of.
Satou-kun.
I’m not making it for you.
I know, it’s just that Kyouko-san’s happiness is mine as well.
Thank you, Satou-kun.
That’s great.
Satou-san, you’re so nice to Yachiyo-san. Do you like her or something?
No way.
You’re right!
So that’s how it is?
Satou-kun is such a great person.
Ah, I found out a nasty secret.
What’s the matter, Otoo?
You look tired.
Ah, Manager...
It gets harder to keep up with them as the years go by, right?
Otoo,
why exactly would you ask me something like that?
S-Sorry...
It’s all very well that everyone is so lively,
but why do my staff have to be so unpleasant?
Well, I’m glad the place is so lively.
Back to work!
Omoidoori nya susumanai
I can’t get as far as I’d like
Koi ni daiji na Communicate
In love, communication is most important
Donna kotoba ga meichuu
What kinds of words would hit the mark?
Kokugo jiten wo mekurou
I’ll flip through a Japanese dictionary
Omomurou ni towazugatari de atsui kimochi wo tsugemashou
Slowly and without warning, I’ll convey these passionate feelings to you
Saredo ingin na kono mune wa jouzetsu ni wa narenai
Or so I thought, as my bashful heart is nowhere near confident enough
Monooto ni Delicate desu mamoru mi no sube shirimasen
I’m delicate to sounds. I don’t even know how to protect myself
Dakedo tantou wa yaomote desu tsune ni genba shobu
But the one in charge takes the full brunt. It’s constantly a battlefield!
Kokoroiki wo takaraka ni jibun Mode de Try shiyou
I’ll louden my disposition and try again in ‘myself’ mode
Heart no Edge ni idomou
I’ll challenge at the edge of my heart
Omou dake mitsumete moshikashitara to At Random
And gaze fixedly at only my feelings. It might come anytime at random
Chance wo matte mirubeki
So it’s best to wait for your chance!
Heart no Ace wo mekurou
I’ll flip over the ace of my heart
Nenriki de mitsumete ai no katachi no Silhouette
And gaze fixedly on my willpower. I’ll search for the image
Image wo saguri dasou
Of the shape of love’s image
Nerai doori ni susumitai
I want to get to where I’m aiming for!
Neko no senaka wo mane shitai
I want to be like the back of a cat
A guy!
Inami-san!
Who is it?! Who is it?!
It’s Otoo-san.
Otoo? Oh, I know.
Thank you for always bringing us
souvenirs, but I heard you were a woman.
Kyouko-san’s such a liar!
Ah!
Huh?
Wh-What should I do... I-I’m about to hit him.
What?! Y-Y-You can’t do that!
Um...
You’re Inami-san, right?
I-Inami-san.
Unlike me, Otoo-san probably isn’t very durable.
It’ll be a big problem if you hit him. Please restrain yourself!
My bones!
A-And if that’s impossible...
Air!
A-Air?
Yes, air! Otoo-san is the most important person here, but he’s never around.
His presence is so weak that
it's like he isn't really here; a bit like air.
It’s a waste of time hitting air!
I-I see.
So, Inami-san. Please introduce yourself to Air-san.
I-I’m Inami Mahiru. Pleased to meet you.
Isn’t this great, Otoo-san? You’re air.
I can’t understand young people these days.
By the way, Inami-san. After this, are you going to...?
I’m so sorry!
Girls are really difficult, aren’t they?
Actually, they’re just annoying, aren’t they?
Next episode preview
Next episode preview:
The Chief is actually quite scary, huh?
Huh, really?
What?! Well, she works properly and is a good person, but...
I wonder when Otoo-san will come back.
I don’t think he’ll be back for a while.
Next: Item 4
Souma, a fresh… too fresh, youth.
Next time: Souma, a fresh… too fresh, youth.
What’s ‘too fresh’ mean, I wonder?