Women’s Changing Room
All right.
Today, I’ll try my best!
Welcome!
It’s all right, Inami-chan. I’ll take care of it.
I’ll show you to your seats right away.
Next time...
Welcome!
It’s all right, Mahiru-chan. I’ll take care of it.
Party of three, correct? Will you be smoking?
N-Next time for sure...
Welco—
Don’t worry, I’m on top of it.
What’s wrong, Inami-chan?
Taneshima-san.
I’ve been working here for a long time,
but because I can only serve female
customers, I’m only able to do half the job.
I’m causing a lot of problems for everyone.
That’s not true!
You think so?
You take care of the female customers perfectly!
But I told myself I’d try my best today.
It’s all right, Inami-chan; the day isn’t over yet!
You still have plenty of chances to recover!
Taneshima-san...
You’re right! All right, I’ll try my best!
That’s the spirit, Inami-chan!
Right!
I’m sorry!
Inami-chan...
Item 5
On a certain sick day, it’s a different Wagnaria.
What are you doing, Takanashi-kun?
Souma-san, I just realized something.
What?
The heights, ages, and weirdness of all the women working here are proportionate.
Degree of weirdness graph
Degree of
weirdness
The smallest, Senpai, is a bit strong-willed, but she’s generally gentle and upright.
Degree of weirdness graph
Degree of
weirdness
Degree of weirdness graph
Degree of
weirdness
Degree of weirdness graph
Degree of
weirdness
Degree of weirdness graph
Degree of
weirdness
Degree of weirdness graph
Degree of
weirdness
Degree of weirdness graph
Degree of
weirdness
Next is Inami-san. She looks normal, but has severe androphobia and will hit a man just for coming close.
Degree of
weirdness
Degree of weirdness graph
Degree of
weirdness
Degree of weirdness graph
Degree of
weirdness
Degree of weirdness graph
Degree of
weirdness
Degree of weirdness graph
Degree of
weirdness
Degree of weirdness graph
Degree of
weirdness
Degree of weirdness graph
Degree of
weirdness
Degree of weirdness graph
Degree of
weirdness
Degree of weirdness graph
Degree of
weirdness
Degree of weirdness graph
Degree of
weirdness
Degree of weirdness graph
Degree of
weirdness
Degree of weirdness graph
Degree of
weirdness
Degree of weirdness graph
Degree of
weirdness
Man
Degree of weirdness graph
Degree of
weirdness
Degree of weirdness graph
Degree of
weirdness
Degree of weirdness graph
Degree of
weirdness
Degree of weirdness graph
Degree of
weirdness
Degree of weirdness graph
Degree of
weirdness
Degree of weirdness graph
Degree of
weirdness
Degree of weirdness graph
Degree of
weirdness
Degree of weirdness graph
Degree of
weirdness
Degree of weirdness graph
Degree of
weirdness
Degree of weirdness graph
Degree of
weirdness
Then there’s the chief, Todoroki-san.
Degree of
weirdness
She’s thoughtful, great with people,
and she performs her work flawlessly.
But that huge sword...
Degree of weirdness graph
Degree of
weirdness
Finally, at the extreme end of the spectrum,
Degree of weirdness graph
Degree of
weirdness
Degree of weirdness graph
Degree of
weirdness
Degree of weirdness graph
Degree of
weirdness
Degree of weirdness graph
Degree of
weirdness
Degree of weirdness graph
Degree of
weirdness
Degree of weirdness graph
Degree of
weirdness
Degree of weirdness graph
Degree of
weirdness
Degree of weirdness graph
Degree of
weirdness
there’s the arrogant and violent manager who only eats and doesn’t do any work.
Ow.
Who’s extreme?
Manager, since when did you...?
I’m not really sure what you’re talking about, but I don’t want to hear that I’m extreme from a pervert like you.
What? If you compare me to all the others, I hardly register.
The restaurant manager, Otoo-san, is
a great person, but he can’t take any pressure,
and he’s always absent from
the restaurant in search of his missing wife.
Satou-san is pretty blunt and has a mean
expression in his eyes, but he’s surprisingly kind.
But he likes the chief...
Souma-san is sociable and seems
like he would get along with anyone.
However, he somehow knows
everything about us and gives off an evil aura.
You’re so mean for saying that in front of the person in question.
The other day, even you—
I’m sorry! You’re a great person!
Anyway, putting that aside,
I do my job properly, and there’s nothing I’m particularly bad at.
Sensible Person
As I thought, I’m definitely the most normal person here!
You seem to have a lot of confidence in that fact.
So stupid.
Manager, what’s that?
Th-This is...
It’s a toy that comes with items on the children’s menu.
Please give me one!
Like I said, it’s for the children’s menu; you can’t have one unless you order something.
Then I’ll order!
You’re being kind of gross, so no.
You two get back to work.
Right, work, work.
I’m hungry.
Kyouko-san!
Yachiyo, a parfait please.
Yes, with pleasure!
I’ll make it strawberry-flavored today.
Good morning, Satou-san!
Hey, Taneshima.
Don’t you seem bit taller?
Really?!
Nope, I lied.
Really, you’re terrible! Stop teasing me!
At it again, aren’t you, Satou-san?
Stop teasing me! Meanie!
Satou-kun never gets tired of that, huh?
That’s true.
It happens like this, doesn’t it?
Every time Todoroki-san shows affection
towards the manager by taking care of her,
Satou-kun picks on Taneshima-san if she happens to be around.
Such is the circle of life.
Yes, it’s quite an impressive vicious cycle.
What’s with you?! You’re always
making fun of me because I’m small!
I’m not.
I’ll get taller!
By the way, what are you going to do when you get taller?
Do you plan on becoming a giant and crushing us?
Big Giant Poplardon
Such villainy, you evil girl.
I’m not evil!
Help me, Katanashi-kun!
I’m sorry, Senpai, I can’t.
Huh? Even though he’s come to my rescue before...
Wh-Why?
Could it be that he’s blackmailing you?
Senpai, I’ve...
realized that you’re painfully cute when you’re being teased.
You traitor!
Fine, I won’t rely on you. I’ll just have someone else help me.
Angry Senpai is so cute.
Yachiyo-san!
What’s wrong, Popura-chan?
Yachiyo-san, Satou-san is bullying me!
Oh my.
You shouldn’t bully the weak.
Who’s bullying who? Sheathe your katana.
Geez, is there something that
puts you in a foul mood every day?
There isn’t.
Sorry.
Satou-kun, every since I asked if you liked Kyouko-san, you’ve been kind of scary.
I know I was wrong, but do you know anything, Souma-kun?
I’m not sure if I’m allowed to tell you this,
but even Satou-kun has someone he likes.
Someone who isn’t the manager.
Then he must have been angry at my misunderstanding.
So? Who is this person he likes?
It’s you...
is what I’d like to say, but Satou-kun silenced me.
Um, here’s a hint: You should think of why he teases Taneshima-san.
Judging by this reaction, she’s not getting it.
I’m sorry, Satou-kun.
Satou-kun...
What?
I’m sorry for asking you if you like Kyouko-san.
I told you, it’s fine.
So, um... uh...
You like Popura-chan, right?
U-Um...
Todoroki...
Ow...
You should stop talking.
Um...
Stop talking!
Sorry, Satou-san, I bumped into you.
Sorry, Taneshima.
You’re so small that I completely missed you.
What’s with you?!
Making fun of me again!
Someone please do something.
This is just getting worse.
I ask you day after day, but are you
truly trying to fix your androphobia?!
I am! I’m working hard at it. I’m better than before!
So, how close have you been able to get to a guy?
A-About 2 meters.
Anyway, I can do it. I get better as people praise me!
What kind of retort was that?
Katanashi-kun, why did you get into a fight with Inami-chan?
Well, the usual reason, but I guess I got irritated because there’s no progress.
But Inami-chan is always trying hard.
I’m going back to work.
Katanashi-kun...
I’m fine, that was only the third punch so far today.
He’s getting used to it.
It pisses me off.
Even though he’s younger... even though I’m his senior...
and it’s not like I can’t do my job!
Mahiru-chan, what’s wrong?
I’m going to do my best.
Just as the manager says, I’ll get
used to Takanashi-kun, and men.
Even if it means the death of Takanashi-kun!
There’s no need to stake anyone’s life on it.
I don’t really understand, but don’t break the wall, okay?
Your fever hasn’t gone down since this morning.
Sorry, Onii-chan, I was resting properly, but...
It’s fine.
More importantly, the clinic is still open, so let’s go and have you checked up.
But what about your job?
I’ll just tell them I’m taking the day off.
I’m sorry.
All right, I understand.
Inami.
Yes?
Takanashi’s little sister is sick, so he’s taking the day off to bring her to the clinic.
What? Oh, is that so?
Mahiru-chan, it seems that Takanashi-kun isn’t coming in today.
Oh, the manager just told me.
Inami-chan, Katanashi-kun has the day off today.
Why is everyone telling me?
Because without Katanashi-kun, you’re...
It’s fine.
Really?
Aren’t you lonely? Don’t you feel like hitting someone?
Geez, I’m not a dog that lost its owner.
I’m fine without Takanashi-kun.
Completely fine.
I wonder if that’s really true...
Huh? Lately, I’ve only been hitting Takanashi-kun.
Man, Takanashi-kun is off today.
With him gone, the odds of me getting hit increases.
Speaking of which, you never get hit, do you, Satou-kun?
Well, that’s because I plan ahead and every day I’m thinking of new methods to handle it.
You’re overly scared of Inami.
Though, she is indeed scary.
Really?
Just think of it as a restaurant attraction where someone suddenly attacks you.
Well, I can’t be that positive.
I wonder if I can just get closer to her.
Just simulate in your head what you’d do if you saw her.
For example, let’s say you encounter Inami while you’re organizing the storage area.
And after that?
Figure it out yourself.
Sorry!
Uh-oh, you made her cry.
Is that the sort of thing you say in this situation?
I did it again. I wonder why I’m like this all the time.
And I even forgot to leave my cellphone in my locker.
I wonder who it is.
Hello?
Hello, it’s Souma.
Sou-Souma-san?! Um... I’m really sorry about earlier!
It doesn’t bother me.
B-But, um...
how did you know my number?
Don’t worry about it.
Actually, I thought you’d hang up on me right away. We’re able to talk now, huh?
Yeah, that’s true.
Things didn’t go like this before.
Really? I wonder if I’m getting better?
Yeah, perhaps thanks to your owner, Takanashi-kun.
I-Inami-san? What was that sound?
Um... I broke the wall.
It’s because you said something weird.
Wall...
Um, it’s not what you think.
I mean, well, it’s true that Takanashi-kun has been taking care of me, but I'm not his dog!
What’s wrong?
Well, even over the phone, I’m still getting beaten up.
Huh?
What are you doing, Inami?
As you can see, I’m on the phone!
It looks more like you’re destroying the building.
Anyway, get out on the floor. It’s almost time for the lunch rush.
Yachiyo got off early and Takanashi’s not coming in today.
Right...
Have you decided what you’ll be ordering yet?
Hey, she’s essentially a good girl, right?
Huh?
Were you able to get along with Inami?
I think our hearts got a
little closer—cell phones sure are amazing!
Good for you.
With this, I’ll never have to come face-to-face with her!
Is that getting closer or further from her?
Looks like there are a lot of customers now.
Yeah, and with Takanashi-kun absent, it looks like the floor is going to get busy.
Sure does.
As luck would have it, on a day like this,
most of the customers are going to be guys.
Welcome!
Table for two, correct?
Welcom—
Table for eleven, correct?
Please wait a moment.
Why is it only guys?!
Huh, the customers are all...?
Only male customers are coming in, and Taneshima-san is getting swamped.
Can the kitchen staff help deal with customers?
You heard her.
Impossible; I hate dealing with customers.
Muster your courage and do your best, Inami!
M-Me?
I’ll hit them!
I’m begging you...
That wasn’t a plea, it was more like...
a threat.
For the time being, I called Yachiyo, but she lives fairly far away, so it’ll be a while till she gets here.
K-Kyouko-san, can you help out on the floor?
You mean me?
I don’t mind, but...
you might regret it though.
Are you okay with that?
Men’s changing room
And thus...
We’ll deal with the customers.
So you handle the orders or make the desserts—whatever you can do.
Yes.
And don’t cry.
Manager, you get on the register.
Right.
Taneshima, try your best.
I’ll do my best!
We have to be enthusiastic in these situations, right?
Three, two, one, go!
Huh?
Satou-kun, that looks good on you.
Shut up.
It’s already getting dark out.
The clinic was pretty crowded, wasn’t it?
It looked like you were about to faint when it came time to get your shot.
Yeah; I really don’t like getting shots.
You get plenty of rest tonight after you’re settled in.
Yeah, I will.
I left in the middle of work...
Are they going to be alright without me?
Maybe I went a bit too far with Inami-san yesterday.
Thank you very much!
So, in the end,
Kyouko-san took care of the register, but
Popura-chan couldn’t handle all the customers by herself.
I did try my best.
Satou-kun and Souma-kun helped her work the floor.
Hey, Satou-kun, smoking isn’t allowed in the kitchen.
Shut up.
Really...
Then, since the kitchen wasn’t able to keep up with orders, Mahiru-chan ended up working there.
I feel terrible.
You guys made a full rotation, huh?
All the customers have left, so there was no reason for you to come.
Sorry, Yachiyo.
It’s fine!
I-I’m sorry!
This was all my fault.
Whatever.
And you even helped out in the kitchen.
If you feel guilty, hurry up and overcome your phobia.
Yes, I’m sorry!
Now, now, don’t worry.
It’s not like Satou-kun is angry.
He was just embarrassed, being out in front of the customers.
It must have been tough.
If Takanashi had been here, I think it would have worked out just fine.
Good work, everyone.
Katanashi-kun! What are you doing here?
My sister is feeling better, so I was wondering if there was anything I could help out with.
You don’t have to worry. We all worked really hard, so everything was all right.
I’m just glad your sister got better.
I’m sorry for causing trouble for everyone. Here are some sweets.
All right, I forgive you.
That’s not just for you!
It’s a gift for everyone, okay?
I’ve caused you a lot of trouble too, Inami-san.
By the way, why are you wearing a kitchen uniform?
Oh, yeah... There’s a reason for this.
Um, I’m sorry for the other day.
I think I said too much last time.
No, I’m sorry too. I always, you know... end up hitting you.
Help yourself to some of the sweets too, before the manager eats them all.
Okay, thank you.
Satou-san, Souma-san, I’m very sorry.
There’s nothing to worry about.
It can’t be helped if your sister was sick.
So, why are you two wearing the floor uniform?
Well, a lot happened.
Seems like Satou-san is in a bad mood...
A lot happened.
Satou-kun, you’re so nice.
You don’t take your stress out on the girls, or even Takanashi-kun.
You must have really hated dealing with the customers.
I can’t get as far as I’d like
Omoidoori nya susumanai
In love, communication is most important
Koi ni daiji na Communicate
What kinds of words would hit the mark?
Donna kotoba ga meichuu
I’ll flip through a Japanese dictionary
Kokugo jiten wo mekurou
Slowly and without warning, I’ll convey these passionate feelings to you
Omomurou ni towazugatari de atsui kimochi wo tsugemashou
Or so I thought, as my bashful heart is nowhere near confident enough
Saredo ingin na kono mune wa jouzetsu ni wa narenai
I’m delicate to sounds. I don’t even know how to protect myself
Monooto ni Delicate desu mamoru mi no sube shirimasen
But the one in charge takes the full brunt. It’s constantly a battlefield!
Dakedo tantou wa yaomote desu tsune ni genba shobu
I’ll louden my disposition and try again in ‘myself’ mode
Kokoroiki wo takaraka ni jibun Mode de Try shiyou
I’ll challenge at the edge of my heart
Heart no Edge ni idomou
And gaze fixedly at only my feelings. It might come anytime at random
Omou dake mitsumete moshikashitara to At Random
So it’s best to wait for your chance!
Chance wo matte mirubeki
I’ll flip over the ace of my heart
Heart no Ace wo mekurou
And gaze fixedly on my willpower. I’ll search for the image
Nenriki de mitsumete ai no katachi no Silhouette
Of the shape of love’s image
Image wo saguri dasou
I want to get to where I’m aiming for!
Nerai doori ni susumitai
I want to be like the back of a cat
Neko no senaka wo mane shitai
Next episode preview
Next episode preview: Next time my sisters are up!
Sou-chan, I wonder if I’m all right?
Eh?
I’m completely worn out before my deadline, and my room is dirty.
You’re fine, or at least you’re better than Kozue-neesan.
Hm?
Next time: “Souta’s melancholy, the women of the Takanashi family.”
Next: Item 6
Souta’s melancholy, the women of the Takanashi family.
I’ll do my best!