Good morning, Yamada here.
Due to certain circumstances, I am currently residing in Wagnaria's attic.
But my true identity is a super waitress!
And Yamada's perfect and glamorous day is just beginning.
Perfect was a lie. I'm sorry!
Hey, Yamada! Hurry and get up.
Aoi-chan.
Manager, Yachiyo-san, good morning.
If you're going to use the water to get ready,
please do so before the rest of the staff get here.
Hurry up.
Okay.
This is how Yamada's day starts.
When evening comes, the usual part-timers arrive.
What's wrong, Taneshima-san?
You're like a maiden in love.
I hope Katanashi-kun comes soon.
Good morning.
Katanashi-kun!
Ah, you look cute as usual today, Senpai.
It makes me so happy when you compliment me.
Let's work hard today.
Oh, he's so dreamy!
What is it?
Nothing.
I was just wondering if you had a fever.
Hm?
I knew that Taneshima-san was quite fond of the cross-dressed Takanashi-san,
but have those feelings transferred to the normal Takanashi-san?
But Inami-san also likes Takanashi-san.
Could this be a love triangle?
But Takanashi-san likes small things,
so would he choose Taneshima-san?
Then, that would mean that Takanashi-san and Taneshima-san would start dating!
They wouldn't look good together at all!
Yamada-san, watch out for your fingers!
Thank goodness, it didn't cut your skin.
What? You don't have to cry.
You're not hurt.
But Inami-san is so nice and pretty...
Wh-What is this all of a sudden?
and her breasts are so small.
What?!
Um, should I be angry now?
If things got messy, I wonder if they would fight each other?
But Yamada likes both of them.
Yamada's
Imagination
~Wagnaria News~
Love triangle mudslinging
occurring at a local restaurant!!
You're horrible, Taneshima-san!
I was the first to fall in love with him!
Don't be so naïve, Inami-chan.
Love isn't about fairness; it's about making your move first!
I've lost.
As expected, bigger breasts are...
I don't like this.
Huh?
Um...
What's going on?
You're acting weird, Yamada-san.
The truth is that Taneshima-san...
Inami-chan!
Taneshima-san!
This might make you angry, but I can't hold it in anymore.
I'm going to confess my love!
I-I don't really understand what's going on, but good luck!
You can't cheer for her if you don't know what's happening!
Katanashi-kun.
Item 11
Yachiyo and Satou Back Then. And, Welcome to the Takanashi Household.
Um...
What's the matter, Senpai?
I-I have a present for you.
Will you accept it?
Huh? Sure.
Present?
I can't reach up there so squat down, squat down.
Huh? What?!
Katanashi-kun, I...
Yes?
This is... how I feel!
What is this, Senpai?
I thought you might look good with black hair...
Not that!
What did you plan on doing with this wig?!
It's just that...
the cross-dressed Katanashi-kun is so...
Pretty, cute, cool, and tall.
You're precisely my ideal woman!
That's a man.
I've been trying to hold it in for days now, but I can't any longer.
It's okay if it's just once in a while,
but I wish you would dress up as a woman.
I can work harder if I can see my goal.
I refuse.
Inami-chan, I got rejected.
I was punished for getting ahead of myself.
I-I don't know what to say...
Taneshima-san, I don't know if it's my place to say, but cross-dressing is not something that boys enjoy doing.
Katanashi-kun.
I'm sorry.
I'll forgive you because you're so cute.
Then will you dress up as a girl?
I told you I won't!
Darn.
So that's what it was.
Yamada totally thought that Taneshima-san fell in love with Takanashi-san.
I was both excited and worried that a love triangle was going to form.
So you were excited?
Katanashi-kun, huh?
Well, Katanashi-kun is younger than me.
In a relationship, younger is a bit…
What?! Yeah, yeah. I look like the younger one, right?!
16 years old
17 years old
Katanashi-kun! Look, look!
What is it?
If it's about cross-dressing, I'm not interested.
No! Souma-san brought it in.
He said they're old pictures of Kyouko-san and everyone from years ago.
Wow.
They're so young.
Right?
How nostalgic.
Yeah.
Souma sure brought in something strange.
Did we even take these photos?
Souma wasn't even working with us at the time.
Just what is he?
So young!
Looking back, Satou-kun looks so cute.
Cute?
How?
Oh, it's so nostalgic.
When we first met, Satou-kun was like...
Nice to meet you.
a delinquent and so scary.
Th-That's discrimination.
Ex-delinquent
Speaking of which, you were also...
Me?
I-I'm Todoroki Yachiyo.
kinda scary.
And really weird.
How?!
How was I scary?!
I forgot.
I don't really care, but I feel like I'm being avoided.
She's fine with the rest of the older staff but...
Oh.
Yachiyo used to get bullied a lot by kids her age.
She probably thinks you're a bully.
I can't believe I'm being hated for something I didn't do.
You need something?
Um...
Kyouko-san wants us to get along.
Kyouko-san is the manager, right?
I'm the type of person who can't get along with others unless instructed to do so.
I was kidding!
Don't cry.
Really?
Um, this is just something that Kyouko-san said,
but she told me we're were the same age.
This is the first time I've worked with someone my own age.
Please be nice.
Love struck
Such good memories.
The old me was too shallow.
A lot of people have come and gone since then, but we basically haven't changed, have we?
That's true.
I wish we could stay like this forever.
Like this forever
Unrequited love forever
A sigh?!
Wouldn't it be great to spend our time like this forever?
Right?
Of course not.
You might be here forever, but the rest of us will all move on someday.
You too?
Of course.
I'm going to get back to work.
Won't you become a "freeter" and work part-time here with me?
No way.
What's wrong, Yachiyo?
Kyouko-san.
Well, Satou-kun said he'll quit working here eventually, and I kind of got depressed.
A lot of part-timers have quit already.
Though our current members have been around a while.
Oh, you're right.
Of course I was sad when the others quit, but...
Huh?
K-Kyouko-san will always be with me, right?
Yeah.
But it's not like Satou is going to leave this instant or anything.
It'll be all right, so get back to work.
Y-You're absolutely right.
I've got to get back to work.
Silly me!
Hey! Don't spill!
Hm?
Do you have something on your mind?
Yeah, it's like I've got something caught in my throat.
Huh?
Maybe you ate too many hard-boiled eggs.
Oh...
Now I want some hard-boiled eggs.
What happened to your contemplation?
Good morning.
Oh yeah, Takanashi.
Yes?
An acquaintance of yours is here.
An acquaintance?
You know, the one who was here before.
The one from your area.
Huh? From my area?
Souta!
Oh, Katanashi-kun!
Why didn't you tell me?
A-About what?
You said she was a lady from your neighborhood.
But you guys have the same last name.
It's such a uncommon name too.
This is such a coincidence!
Right! It's quite a coincidence!
As expected of Senpai!
I-I'll do the rest, so leave it to me.
Okay.
Then I'll leave the rest to you.
Jeez, why did you have to interrupt?
What do you mean "Why"?!
What are you doing here?!
Hurry up and leave!
Leave now!
Well fine then.
I'll just shout childhood stories about you as I leave.
Please stay.
Really, why did you come here?
All you're doing is drinking beer.
If you just want to drink, go do it somewhere else.
I came here to watch you work.
You're after that teeny girl, aren't you?
What of it?
If you're bored, go to your boyfriend's house or something.
You sure got lucky with such a fun workplace.
Oh, I see, you got dumped.
That was fast.
He should have told me beforehand if he doesn't like the German suplex!
That'll be 3,500 yen.
Put it on my tab.
Family restaurants don't have tabs.
I'll come again!
Fine, I'll pay for it, so don't ever come back.
Don't ever come here again!
Just how much did she drink?
A few days later
There are no other complaints!
Right...
Orders are served quickly and the girls are cute!
Thank you very much...
But I just can't let this slide.
There aren't enough varieties of alcohol!
We're a family restaurant...
Why don't you have any Japanese wine or liqueur?
Looks like she's here again.
Damn her!
I'm sorry, Takanashi-kun.
Takanashi-kun?
Takanashi-kun!
I, who hit Takanashi-kun once again today, have decided to reflect on my recent actions.
If it meant that Takanashi-kun would continue to care about me,
I thought it would be okay to continue hitting guys.
But I'm causing too much trouble for everyone,
and I've already hit him three other times today.
I know that I need to fix this.
But I'm still only thinking about what's convenient for me.
When I started running, after leaving everybody behind, my legs suddenly got heavy and...
Huh?
when I looked at my leg, there was a bloody hand.
Scary Stories That Actually Happened
What are you doing with the lights off?
We're closing up.
One of the customers left this book behind.
We're having a ghost story competition in the break room!
Taneshima.
Y-Yes?!
When looking in the rear-view mirror, a woman without a head appeared in the back.
Every night while sleeping, you grow shorter and shorter.
One day, a bear...
You're just getting scared by reflex.
Satou-san, you idiot.
Now I'm too scared to go home.
Please don't scare Senpai.
It's my fault?
I guess it can't be helped.
Since it's late, I'll give you a ride home.
I'm going to change, so wait here.
Thank you, Satou-san.
Now then, we should get going too, Inami-san.
Right.
Manager.
Please walk Yamada home.
You live here.
Oh, right.
I'm sorry for making you stay out so late with me.
Taneshima-san wouldn't let go of my hand.
I don't mind.
I have tomorrow off, anyway.
But really, Senpai is the only one who would get scared by such a simple ghost story.
O-Of... course.
Y-You're wrong!
I'm not scared at all.
I'm totally fine.
I'm sorry! I'm scared!
I'm sorry!
Even though my existence is scarier than that of a ghost, I'm sorry for being scared!
You don't have to torture yourself like that.
I'm sorry.
I'm scared of ghosts regardless of their gender.
The same goes for Senpai, but if you're scared you shouldn't keep listening.
I'll walk you all the way home today then.
I usually just walk with you halfway.
N-No it's fine. I'd feel bad.
Besides, my mom isn't home today, so eventually I'll be home... alone...
I-It'll be fine.
What will be?
Want to come to my house then?
I didn't mean it like that.
I understand, but I'm still worried.
About your house...
I appreciate the thought, but I'd rather not.
Well, I won't force you.
Wh-Why are you stopping?
It seems like someone's following us.
You're just trying to scare me by lying.
Stupid!
I'm not lying.
Listen! You can hear it.
Please tell me you're lying!
I-I'm sorry.
I could be imagining it.
I-I'm scared.
What should we do?
I'm scared too... of you.
But wait, we just have to turn around and confirm it for ourselves.
Just like that?
I see it.
Really? No!
I see Yamada.
I was too scared to be in the attic all alone.
You were scared too?
So that's why you followed us?
Satou-san and the manager all left by car so...
You don't have to cry anymore, Yamada-san.
I'm sorry, Inami-san.
I'm sorry for interrupting!
Hey wa—!
Okay, I'll have Yamada-san stay at my house tonight then, okay?
Will you really be all right?
We'll be fine.
Even if we're scared when we're alone, it'll be fine if there are two of us.
Boo!
Tremble
You two aren't okay.
My oldest sister is away on a business trip,
and the next eldest is locked up in her room,
so you don't need to feel uncomfortable.
Yay, it's a sleepover!
You're awfully nice today.
Why?
Even though Yamada-san's here.
It can't be helped.
Besides, Inami-san and Yamada will...
Yay, Inami-chan and Yamada-chan.
Oh, the regular customer.
What, what?
You're scared of ghosts so you're staying here?
That's fine, stay over, stay over!
I was so bored!
I just thought that I could get a lot of housework done if you two keep Kozue-neesan company.
So that's how it was.
I see, it's a sleepover.
Please make yourselves at home, okay?
Oh, just a second.
Here are some pajamas.
My sisters' are probably too big, so please use mine.
Nazuna-chan is so mature for a grade-schooler.
Mom and dad's room are open...
I'm sorry for waking you, Nazuna.
Let's go to sleep.
O-Okay...
So she is in elementary school after all...
All right! So how about we take a bath.
Let's go in together.
That's impossible!
Yamada wants to!
Don't worry! Our bath is huge.
It's small!
I said it was big...
I sure am making progress.
Takanashi-kun.
Yes?
Thanks for the bath.
Is something wrong?
Nothing.
It's so big.
Huh?
Oh, the bath?
So small.
P-Putting that aside,
Is there anything I can help you with?
Nope.
I'm pretty much finished.
You've already helped out a lot by keeping Kozue-neesan occupied.
Please make yourself comfortable.
Although, you don't have to get that comfortable.
Does she think this is her own house?
Yamada will live here!
Will you?
Yamada-san...
I'll be going to my room then. Have a nice night.
Good night.
This is the first time I've seen Souta get along so well with a girl his own age.
Think carefully before letting out other people's secrets, okay?
Thinking
Inami-san likes Takanashi-kun.
Seriously?!
Seriously.
I've always thought that.
What are they talking about?
All right!
Then I, Kozue-oneesan, will subtly and artfully assist Inami-chan!
Jeez, Kozue-neesan and Yamada are sure doing as they please.
Do they want me to get hit?
Well, I'll allow it since you always listen to my complaints about my family and stuff.
Wh-What?!
Me too!
You're always willing to help me fix my androphobia,
and you've helped me out with my father,
but I'm always causing trouble,
and today's the same too!
Everything's always my fault!
They didn't make you drink, did they?
You don't have to be so disheartened.
U-Um, Takanashi-kun.
Yes?
Can I ask you something?
Go ahead.
Is it about classic literature?
Taneshima-senpai is better with science and math.
That's not it.
U-Um...
Yes? What is it?
Even after my androphobia is cured, will you still ca-
talk with me?
Well, if you stop hitting me, I'm certain we'll get along even better.
I know, right?
Hm?
Huh?
Was I over-thinking it?
I don't really understand, but it looks like you're scared of ghosts anymore.
Oh, I forgot about that.
I'm not sleepy yet, so do you want to do this?
B-But will I be able to do it?
It'll be fine.
But this is my first time.
This is getting good.
What are they doing?
There's only one thing a boy and a girl do behind closed doors.
Oh! I know!
Card games?
Yamada wants to play too!
Jeez, Yamada-chan.
Kozue-neesan, you're too noisy.
The Old Maid...
So you really were doing that?!
What a boring guy.
Old Maid
Next episode preview
Next episode preview:
Senpai?!
Katanashi-kun! Don't you think that I haven't been getting much screen time lately?
What? Th-That's not true.
It's true!
Cross-dress for poor little me!
Rage
That's totally unrelated!
Poke
Next time, An unexpected night before the match. Taneshima's repayment.
Next: Item 12
An unexpected night before the match. Taneshima's Repayment.
Kotori-chan, come back!