[Wilting]
OP
[An unexpected night before the match. Taneshima's Repayment.]
[Inside the girl's locker room]
[Tall, Busty, Slim, Amazing]
[Girl's locker room]
[He likes you way more than me]
[Grow~]
[Errr]
[Rage]
[Impossible]
[Seems fun]
[Flash]
[Poke]
[Stab]
[Issues]
[And now, the night before the date]
[Takanashi]
[Love-Talk at Family Restaurants by Ei]
[Romance Novel by Ei]
[The other side of the rainbow by Ei]
[Yellow Happiness by Ei]
[The Scramble Intersection of Love by Kazeyama Mamoru]
[The Back You Want To Get To Know by Kazeyama Mamoru]
ED
[A decisive battled called date. Katanashi, Inami, and also...]
I said I would reimburse you for the magic hand.
You don't have to.
It was my fault for scaring you.
B-But don't you need it?
Like, to go home and stuff.
I know we need one. That's why I've already bought another one.
Also, there was a promotion going on...
...so I got two.
You really need it?!
And two of them?!
Well, I feel like I benefited, so don't worry about it.
Benefited...
What are you talking about?
Oh, Senpai.
I-It's nothing.
What the...
To tell you the truth, last night, Yamada and Inami-san...
Aoi-chan!
I don't really think we need to hide the fact that we went to your house last night.
I feel bad for Taneshima-san.
We can't.
The stuff about my sisters and
my past could leak from anywhere.
So everything about my family is a secret from Senpai.
But she looks so sad.
Is that all right?
You're right.
A sad Senpai is all right too.
I didn't mean it like that.
Well then, good work everyone.
Huh? You sure are in a hurry today, Katanashi-kun.
You're not going home with Inami-chan?
No, the soy sauce is on special sale today.
Soy sauce?
Yes!
It may already be sold out since they're about to close.
But I don't want to give up till the very end!
Good luck.
Yes!
I lost to soy sauce.
She sure is dreamy.
Slim, tall, mature-looking.
And, on top of being cute, has a cool ambience about her.
Katanashi-kun is the ultimate woman, right?
If he wasn't a guy.
Not really my type, though.
Anyway, you're still bringing this up?
Are you into girls or something?
We already have enough of that with Todoroki.
No, you've got it all wrong!
It's not love, it's a matter of aspiration!
Um... How to put it...
Like tall, busty, slim, and amazing!
I just want to become someone like that.
First of all, you'll need to get taller.
So I need to grow...
Being tall isn't all it's cracked up to be. You hit your head all the time.
You stand out whether you like it or not.
You can reach almost anything.
You'll feel out of place at movies or when
watching fireworks, but you can see really well.
You can breathe easier in packed trains
because you're one head taller than everyone else.
Now you're just bragging!
I hope he'll dress up as a girl again.
I doubt he'll do it anymore.
But you know, I remember that Inami-chan could touch Katanashi-kun when he was cross-dressed.
So Inami-chan will be able to get closer to
Katanashi-kun, and I can receive some of her hot-girl aura.
Everyone will be happy if Katanashi-kun cross-dresses!
But Takanashi will be miserable.
You're right...
Well, cross-dressing won't be happening.
I wonder if he keeps things from me because I think about these things.
Who knows.
Does he not like me?
That's not true, Taneshima-san!
Inami-chan?
He just doesn't want you finding out about his sisters.
If anything, he likes you.
He likes you way more than me.
Inami-chan? Your voice is shaking.
You're tiny.
So Inami's probably right about him liking you.
You think so?
This is... Katanashi-kun's student notebook.
His train pass is in here. He must have dropped it.
He's going to need it tomorrow.
I've got to deliver it to his house.
Will you be all right by yourself?
My shift's not over, so I can't give you a ride.
Yeah, I'll be fine.
It seems his house isn't far from here.
I'm off!
It'll be bad if she meets Kozue-san at his house.
But I'm still dressing, so I can't get out!
So this is Katanashi-kun's house.
It's bigger than mine.
It's amazing. Does he have a huge family?
Yes?
So tall!
So tiny!
C-Cross-dressed Katanashi-kun?
No, it isn't.
His sister?
U-Um...
I-I'm sorry.
She's definitely Katanashi-kun's sister.
Wh-What is this cute little thing?
So, did you need something?
U-Um, the train pass.
Hey, It's Taneshima-chan!
You're right.
Good evening.
Katanashi's regular customer and
Katanashi-kun's little sister, Nazuna-chan.
Seeing that they live together like this must mean that they're all...
Katanashi-kun's family?!
It's Takanashi.
I was able to get some soy sauce, but I lost my train pass.
Did I leave it at work?
I've got to go to school tomorrow without my train pass.
Damn, what a waste.
S-Senpai?!
Why are you here?
I knew that Nazuna-chan was your really tall little sister,
but, beside the fact that our regular drunken customer is really also your older sister,
you also have another really tall older sister!
There's also one more older sister.
F-For the time being...
...I'm going to worship you!
We're not blessed by the gods!
What's wrong, Taneshima-san?
Yesterday, Katanashi-kun...
Takanashi-kun?
Well, you know... Kozue-neesan is totally pathetic.
How rude!
I was worried that you'd make fun
of me or dislike me if you found out.
I wouldn't think of anything so mean...
Katanashi-kun doesn't trust me.
I lost my confidence as a Senpai.
You had confidence...?
Um, it seems that I hurt Senpai's feelings.
That's why I told you it wasn't something to hide.
Things got even more complicated.
She's so tiny in that position.
You just thought that a tiny Senpai was cute, didn't you?
I-I didn't think that.
I'm regretful...
I'll go!
But...
It would be better if you apologized sooner rather than later.
I agree.
But when I see her like that,
I just get an urge to take her home.
There are... so many reasons why you shouldn't do that...
Taneshima-san.
Inami-chan.
I'm sure that Takanashi-kun treasures you so much...
...that he couldn't bring himself to
tell you about his embarrasing sisters.
In my case,
he said that he didn't even care if I found out.
Katanashi-kun is so mean!
I feel so bad for you, Inami-chan!
Huh? I meant to soothe her.
A-Anyway, he's always thought of you as his precious Senpai.
Let's forgive him. Okay?
Okay...
Inami-chan.
You're really a great person.
Katanashi-kun doesn't even realize that a really great person like you likes him...
Katanashi-kun is so mean!
Huh?!
Am I pitiful?
Senpai.
I'm sorry...
...for keeping secrets from you.
Katanashi-kun, this has been on my mind for a long time,
but you don't seem to quite understand how I feel.
Nor how Inami-chan feels...
I don't understand your feelings?
Is that true?!
I thought I understood children's feelings.
That's exactly what I'm talking about!
A girl's feelings!
I was angry that you didn't trust me!
I'm sorry.
To make up for it, I'll do anything you want me to.
Huh? Really?
Oh crap!
She might make me cross-dress!
Then...
...go on a date with Inami-chan!
I thought you were going to make me cross-dress.
You don't have to do that, even though I want to see it.
It's for you to understand a girl's feelings.
And as an expression of gratitude for
Inami-chan always taking care of me.
I can understand the feelings part,
but why is the date an expression of gratitude for Inami-san?
I-It'll be a great opportunity to fix her androphobia.
How about this?
Souma-san!
You go on a date while cross-dressing.
Don't say that with a smile on your face!
Just think about it.
I don't have to think about it to know that I don't want to!
While it would be nice if her first date was with a guy,
if, by chance, there was someone
that Inami-san actually started to like,
wouldn't you want her to be able to go on her first date with him?
So, if you cross-dress, it'll barely count.
Souma-san.
You seem to think that this will be pretty funny.
That's just your imagination.
Besides, Inami-san wouldn't get so nervous if she were with a girl.
How about it, Inami-san?
Taneshima-san, you'll get to see Kotori-chan too.
Souma-san, you're amazing.
You're so smart.
Hey!
Why do I have to cross-dress for someone
Inami-san might fall in love with in the future?
But, being a guy, I wouldn't want to get beaten up by my date...
I should listen to Senpai's request...
And I do want to know how much
Inami-san's androphobia has improved.
I don't want to cross-dress but...
I-I'm fine with the date but...
I... don't want to cross dress.
The date is already decided?!
Wh-What should I do?!
What should I do about the date with Takanashi-kun?!
Noooo!
I-I'm sorry!
Why am I always like this?
I can't go on a date like this.
What are you doing back here, Inami-chan?
Taneshima-san!
Are you all right, Takanashi?
Yeah... somewhat.
Ow.
That one really hurt.
Inami-san is especially dangerous today...
You're right.
And this is the fifth time today.
Yes.
I don't know if I can go on a date with her like this.
Then, just cross-dress!
I'd rather keep getting hit than cross-dress.
So the thought of not going on
the date doesn't even occur to him?
Well, Takanashi-kun is really earnest.
I see.
Going on a date is impossible after all, Taneshima-san.
I've got to call this whole thing off.
Lukewarm!
The tea?
You're lukewarm, Inami-chan!
Your burning passion to cure your androphobia isn't hot enough!
Y-You think so?
Yeah!
You'll never be able to fix it like this!
Inami-chan, do you plan on hitting
Katanashi-kun for the rest of your life?!
Rest of my life... Rest of my life....
That's not the part you should react to!
Inami-chan, you still have time.
You've got to work hard, fix your androphobia,
and succeed on this date.
Taneshima-san.
Right!
I'll work hard.
Good.
But it's also a fact that there's not
a whole lot of time before the date.
We've got to take some drastic measures.
I see, I see.
Rope!
Here!
Rope?!
Handcuffs!
Here!
Yamada-san, why do you have those?!
Mahiru-chan...
Criminal?
Mostly as punishment for hitting guys...
I feel a little bad,
but for the time being, I made sure she couldn't use her hands to hit people.
We'll go test it out on the kitchen staff.
So. Can she work without her hands?
Poplar-chan...
That's how it is.
Inami-chan, as she is now, is safe.
Probably.
Try to touch her!
Yay...
Why are you poking her with chopsticks?!
Fool.
This is a cooking chopstick.
It's longer than an ordinary chockstick.
Why are you poking her with a cooking chopstick?!
Because we're still too scared to use our hands.
Why are you poking me as well?!
Because it's fun.
Why won't you poke Yamada?!
It's kind of lonesome!
Uh... Because we don't have any interest?
Please poke Yamada too!
Taneshima.
Inami falls under Takanashi's jurisdiction, right?
Take her to him.
The wrong jurisdiction?
Right.
It's like a bureaucracy.
On a side note, Souma's in charge of Yamada.
What?!
Please poke me! Please poke me!
And I'm in charge of bullying you.
What?! I don't want you in charge of that!
It's no good.
The people here are useless.
You brought her here without asking, so do what you want.
Looks like we'll have to simulate the actual
event, and have the guy himself cooperate.
A date...
Katanashi-kun!
So you finally did it.
Isn't it a great idea?
To tell you the truth, I've thought of this before.
You have?!
In that case, try touching her, with your bare hands.
Well, I thought about it, but if I do this...
I knew she'd kick me like this.
She powered up!
So basically...
After the experiment, we've confirmed
that if we bind her hands, she'll kick instead.
And, if she can't kick,
she'd probably headbutt or bite.
So we're going to have to fix all the possibilities.
Now there are more issues...
J-Just as I thought,
I think we should call the date off.
Inami-chan.
B-Because it still didn't work out with me like this!
If we go on a date...
I'd probably...
...beat the crap out of Takanashi-kun!
I already know that.
Huh?
I accepted, knowing all that.
So you don't have to worry about it.
Now, let's get back to work.
Katanashi-kun is such a man.
Y-Yeah.
I'll be heading out now.
You two have the day off tomorrow, right?
Yes.
Goodbye.
Bye.
Huh?
Then, I'll see you tomorrow.
Y-Yeah...
You're okay with the time, right?
Yeah. I'll make sure I won't be late.
All right, me too.
See you.
Bye bye.
Tomorrow?
Yeah, I'll be out for a bit.
I'll prepare lunch before I leave.
Oh, okay.
Where are you going, Onii-chan?
Where?
I don't know.
I wonder where Inami-san wants to go.
Huh?!
You're going somewhere with Inami-san?
Yeah.
There's been a lot going on.
And besides, I want to see the result of all our hard work.
Result?
Result must mean...
Does Onii-chan... like getting hit?
It's true.
That...
Hm? What's wrong, Nazuna?
G-Good luck!
All right.
What should I wear tomorrow?
Especially since tomorrow might become a really important day.
What should I do?
What should I wear tomorrow?
What should I bring?
It's my first time on a date, so I don't know!
Which hairpin should I wear tomorrow?
One of the ones I got from Takanashi-kun?
Or the one he complimented for the first time?
But that would be too obvious.
More importantly, we haven't even decided where to go!
I'll look for something at the bookstore and...
It's closed already!
Anyway, the person at the register today is a guy, so even if it was open, I couldn't buy anything!
I've got to find some reference from something in my room.
Romance novel...
And then Shinji hugged Yayoi tightly.
I'm so jealous.
Inami-san!
I'll hug you tightly with these hands!
Mahiru?
Oh my.
Mom!
I thought I heard a lot of noise from your room.
What are you doing with all these clothes out?
I didn't know what to wear tomorrow...
It'll be fine.
You're cute no matter what you wear.
Don't say that...
Also, I got really confused when I was trying to figure out which hairpin to wear and where to go.
I really... don't know...
You look like you're having a lot of fun.
I'm really worried!
It's almost as if you're going on your first date.
You really like Takanashi-san, don't you?
Go to sleep now. You don't want to be tired all day tomorrow.
Okay...
Goodnight.
I haven't solved anything yet!
Not the clothes for tomorrow, nor where to go!
Um, this one?
This?
I wonder if we'll have a clear day tomorrow.
Tomorrow...
I'm going on a date.
I...
...might die.
Next episode preview:
Katanashi-kun, are you all ready for tomorrow?
Yes. I should be perfectly ready for tomorrow.
Make sure you dress up.
Right. Especially since they might end up being my burial clothes.
Next time!
A decisive battle known as a date. Takanashi, Inami, and also...
We're going to check your clothes before the date!
What?!