Welcome!
Table for two.
Would you like the smoking or non-smoking section?
I’ll take smoking.
Very well. This way, please.
Order up.
Okay!
I’ll take it out to table eight.
Hey, is table five ready for their hamburger set?
Oh, I’m sorry.
I’ll go check after I serve this order.
Today’s pretty busy.
It is, isn’t it?
Lately we’ve been a bit understaffed.
Kyouko-san mentioned that
she’ll be hiring a new part-timer.
A new employee, huh?
Which would you prefer, Satou-kun? A guy or a girl?
If it’s regarding work, I don’t care.
Really? Well, I don’t care much either,
but somebody interesting would be nice, don’t you think?
I don’t care. Now finish the next order already.
Right, right.
Oh, I’ll have the combo set’s fries ready in 17 seconds.
Right.
Could it be a cold?
Huh?
Me?
I’ll leave it to you.
Will you be okay, Taneshima-san?
Suddenly being asked to find a new employee...
Yeah... I guess I’ll ask my friends from school.
After that, I’ll probably have to solicit around town.
Will you help me, Inami-chan?
I don’t mind asking friends, but s-soliciting in town is...
I see.
I suppose there’ll be a lot of men around in town, right?
Yeah...
I’m sorry.
Don’t worry! I’ll work hard!
Sorry for the wait.
Oh?
Welcome!
Would you...
Would you be interested in a part-time job?
Um—
Don't worry. Where are your parents?
Parents?
Right, your mom or dad.
I see. It’s suspicious if a complete stranger suddenly offers you a part-time job.
Um, my dad is a civil servant and my mom is a housewife!
Huh? I didn’t mean it like that—
So cute...
Well then, let’s go to the police box over there.
Could it be that he thinks I’m lost?
Um, you’ve got it all wrong! I’m soliciting for a part-time job at a family restaurant.
Would you like to work with me?
Huh?! What should I do?
Playing pretend ‘Family Restaurant’? That’s a bit...
That’s not it!
What should I do...? He’s not getting what I’m saying.
But I probably can’t get anyone else at this point, and somehow he seems like a good person too.
Um...
I’m Taneshima Popura, 17 years old;
a high school student!
High School Student
Huh? A high school student?
Um, you see... I’m looking for
someone who could work part-time.
This ID and uniform...
She’s a senior at my high school? And she’s older than me?!
But she looks to be 12 and she’s so cute... Is this all right?
It is!
I’ll take it—the job.
R-Really?!
Yep.
Hokkaido Branch
‘Wagnaria’ Family Restaurant
Well then, I’ll be working here from now on!
Takanashi Souta
I’m Takanashi Souta, 16 years old.
People often say ‘Shouchouyuu’ and ‘Kotoriasobi’, but it’s ‘Takanashi’.
Taneshima Popura
I’m Taneshima Popura!
I was named in the hope that I would grow like the poplar tree.
Poplar tree...
Since I’m one year older, just ask me if you have any questions.
She’s cute!
We both have unusual names, but let’s try not to get them wrong, okay, Katanashi-kun?
She got it wrong!
I’m the manager, Shirafuji Kyouko.
Shirafuji Kyouko
Have Taneshima introduce you to the other employees.
Leave it to me!
The manager seems kind of scary.
I don’t care if it’s Takanashi or Katanashi, and I don’t give any training, so be warned.
Does that mean I’m supposed to learn by just watching others?
Not really. I just don’t work a lot, so I wouldn’t know.
Eh?
So just ask me when you have questions about work stuff, okay?
Anyway, I’ll leave the rest to you, Taneshima.
Okay!
That’s some manager you have.
Really?
In any case, I’m glad you’re here, Katanashi-kun.
No one responded to our ads, and none of my friends would do it.
The manager left it to me to find a new employee.
Would you be interested in a part-time job?
That was so cute.
Anyway, it must have been fate that led me to you that day, so from now on let’s work hard together, okay, Katanashi-kun?
Um... Senpai?
It’s actually not Katanashi, but Takanashi.
What?! Oh, I’m sorry. Um...
Ta-ka— Ta-ka— Katanashi-kun!
Kata-Kata-Kata—
Oh well...
For starters, I’ll show you how to put the cups away, so watch very carefully.
Yes, Senpai.
This cup goes here, but...
Senpai?
I can’t reach it, so I’ll ask someone else do it.
Eh?
Next, we put these dishes up in the sink.
It’s too heavy to lift,
so I’ll ask someone else do this too.
What is this? I’m still being taught, right?
Hey, Taneshima.
Oh, Satou-san.
Is this the new guy who’s starting today?
Yeah, he is.
I’m Takanashi Souta. Pleased to meet you.
Satou
Jun
I’m Satou Jun. Nice to meet you.
This guy is kind of scary, a bit like the manager.
Satou-san, are you free right now?
What is it? The usual?
It’s too high for me to reach, so please do it for me.
All right.
It’s too heavy for me to lift, so please do it for me.
Right, right.
Well, do you understand now, Katanashi-kun?
You got it, Takanashi-kun?
I think I’ll manage.
Is Satou-san actually a nice guy?
Your hair is so fluffy.
Stop it! Stop it!
You’re Takanashi-kun, the one who’s starting today?
Oh, yes.
I’m Souma Hiromi. Nice to meet you.
Souma Hiromi
Yeah, nice to meet you.
I hear you’re Taneshima’s junior at her high school.
Huh? Yes, that’s right. You knew that?
I’m the senpai.
Huh? Did I tell anybody that I go to the same high school as Taneshima-senpai?
Taneshima-san is in charge of training you?
Yeah! I’m educating him really strictly right now.
You’re great, Taneshima-san.
Hey.
What is it, Satou-kun?
Did you finish preparing?
Not quite...
Let’s hurry and clean up.
Well, work hard, you two!
Souma-san must like gossiping.
Well, he seems like a nice guy too.
Now, Katanashi-kun, time to resume your training.
Yes, Senpai!
Thank you very much!
We usually greet people like this.
Yes, I understand, Senpai.
Popura-chan!
Yachiyo-san!
You’re Takanashi-kun, the new guy?
Yes!
Thank goodness.
I’ve been looking for you to introduce myself.
Wow, she’s beautiful.
I’m Takanashi Souta. Nice to meet you—
I’m Todoroki Yachiyo, the chief.
Todoroki Yachiyo
Don’t hesitate to ask me any questions you might have, Takanashi-kun.
T-Thank you very much.
Table eight seems to be calling for me so I’ll be going now, okay?
I’ll leave it to you.
First of all, I’d like to ask you about that
dangerous thing you’re carrying at your waist.
I do this sort of work at home, so it’s somewhat relaxing.
I kind of fell into this job...
but everybody seems nice, so I guess I’ll try it out for a while.
Katanashi-kun!
Listen to this!
The customer I brought food to said, “Are you in middle school?”
Isn’t that awful?! I’m in high school!
That is awful!
Senpai isn’t in middle school!
Thank you, Katanashi-kun!
You’re an elementary school student.
Eh?!
No, no... I’m in high school.
High school students have to be a little taller, Senpai.
Katanashi-kun, I’m not small!
Katanashi-kun, I’m off!
Right.
Hey, Takanashi.
Yes, what is it, manager?
Let me tell you this one thing. It’s fine for you to get along well with Taneshima,
but don’t get caught up in some love affair.
It’s a real pain to make the shift schedule fit.
There’s no way that’ll happen!
Romance is out of the question.
Is that true?
Satou-san! Don’t just jump into
the conversation like that!
I just heard it.
If it’s not going to happen, then it’s fine.
If anything...
I want to become Senpai’s father.
You’re weird.
Huh?!
Well, don’t do that either...
Is that wrong?!
Of course it is.
I won’t say anything regarding your interests, but don’t do anything weird in the store.
Wait just a minute, you don’t think I’m a lolicon, do you?
You’re not?
I’m not!
I like small and cute things.
Children, puppies, kittens, hamsters, and...
water fleas!
Water fleas?
I want to take care of anything that’s really weak.
Um...
That’s why... I don’t see Senpai as you think I do.
Sure, she’s older, but she’s just like a child or a puppy.
Taneshima-senpai is on the same level as a water flea!
I can’t date a water flea.
Taneshima is the same as a water flea?
You’re quite a terrible guy.
Oh yeah, how old are you, manager?
Twenty eight.
Oh, you’re pretty old, huh?
Wow... I have a shift every day of the week...
You’re young, right?
Good morning.
Good morning, Katanashi-kun.
You’re working today, too?
Every day for the past few weeks...
It’s pretty tough.
Maybe you should tell Kyouko-san?
You’re probably right.
Manager...
Oh, Takanashi-kun. Have you gotten used to the work?
Chief,
I’m quite fine with the work itself, Manager,
but it’s regarding my shift.
What is it? You want to work more?
Eh?
You want to try being floor chief, Takanashi?
Did I do something?
You’re young, so just work ’til you die.
Good luck with your work, Takanashi-kun.
I wonder what the manager’s mad about.
Katanashi-kun, did you do something to Kyouko-san?
Is it because she’s old?
I heard that when you get older your hormone balance gets all messed up.
Menopausal disorder?!
You definitely said something, didn’t you?
Did I say something?
Her attitude’s changed ever since I asked her about her age.
Oh yeah, how old are you, manager?
Twenty eight.
Oh, you’re pretty old, huh?
Katanashi-kun, that’s it!
What? What was it?
You can’t just say “you’re pretty old” to a woman!
But she is. Once you pass 12 years old...
That’s too young!
Oh, don’t worry, Senpai. You’re not old at all.
What?
Anyway, people around that age are especially sensitive about the matter. You can’t say something like that.
So that’s what it was; I need to apologize.
You’re right.
Old people...
Hey, Katanashi-kun!
Katanashi-kun, hurry up and go apologize.
Right, understood, Senpai.
Hey, excuse me.
Huh?
This store has its heater on way too high. Do something about it.
Then get out of this store and burn off that unsightly fat of yours.
What?!
I’m so sorry!
P-Please excuse us!
Why would you pick a fight with a customer?
You just have to say that you’ll turn down the heater.
I’m not wrong.
Be more of a manager!
Actually, be more of an adult.
If you don’t act nicer, we’re going to get a bad reputation.
It’ll be troublesome if this leaks out. In that case...
In that case?
Throw her in the fridge!
What?!
I’ll go serve her something cold.
Huh?
I’m sorry for earlier.
Here’s a drink on the house, and we’ve turned down the heater.
If you’re still unsatisfied, please inform one of our staff.
Oh my, you don’t have to go that far.
Is it really all right?
Well, it does seem a bit cooler than before. Thank you.
No problem. If you need anything else, just let us know.
Please excuse me.
I’m going to stop expecting things from the manager from now on.
Good work!
Um... is the manager always like that?
Yeah, the manager is always like that.
Pretty much.
Please stop it!
What’s with this tiny little thing? This store lets an elementary school kid work here?
Little girl, what grade are you in?
Please stop it! I’m a high school student!
Senpai!
Takanashi-kun.
Yes?
It’s all right.
Leave it to her.
Eh? To whom?
Just watch.
Dear customer.
Manager!
H-Hey, are you okay?
Dear customer, please refrain from violence.
What kind of employee kicks a customer?
Bring the manager!
You have business with me?
Manager
What kind of manager kicks a customer?
We’re never gonna come here again, damn old hag!
I hope this store goes out of business!
Oh, they haven’t paid their bill yet...
Taneshima, it’s okay.
Is it okay for the manager to do that?!
Why not?
More importantly, Takanashi-kun...
Yes?
Can you take the manager’s cell phone to her?
What? This is the manager’s?
Why do you have it?
Here, hurry up.
Ah, all right.
Manager, Souma-san told me to give you this.
You’re calling the police?
Maybe you shouldn’t make such a big deal out of this.
Oh, hey. The customers that just left; take all the money they have on them.
What?!
It’s okay, I have useful juniors.
Who is this manager?!
I bet it’ll be tough for Takanashi-kun from now on.
You’re probably right.
Don’t worry, I’ll make sure
this doesn’t become a big deal.
A big deal...
Kyouko-san, you don’t have to go that far.
They called a working girl like you a “tiny little thing,” you know?
I guess she’s pretty protective of the staff here.
Besides, they called me a hag.
Manager?
Called me a hag... a hag.
Kyouko-san?
This is it!
Manager, um...
What is it?
I’m sorry about earlier, with the whole age thing.
I’ve realized that your youth hasn’t dwindled with age.
Right?
Yes, I understand completely.
Manager, you’re a kid, aren’t you?
Katanashi-kun...
Oh, I have a day off on next week’s schedule.
Katanashi-kun, I’m going to be strict teaching you how to do your job.
But no crying though, okay?
Manager!
Can I hug her?
Absolutely not.
Katanashi-kun, you learn fast but at times you don’t listen to me at all, do you?
Sorry.
Katanashi-kun, you always seem preoccupied with my height, so today I brought in my secret weapon.
No, your height is what I like.
So, what’s this ‘secret weapon’?
A stool!
You’d be okay with this, right, Katanashi-kun?
Now with this we are even, right?
Senpai...
But this isn't practical to carry around with me, so I suppose it's rather useless.
Can I hug you after all?
I told you, absolutely not.
I’m getting pretty used to this job.
Actually, that scares me a bit.
Oh, now that I think about it...
Is something wrong, Katanashi-kun?
Senpai, I work a lot,
but I haven’t worked with this Inami-san at all.
Oh... Um, you see, Inami-chan is—
Hey, Taneshima!
Yes?
Order up!
Okay!
Sorry, Katanashi-kun, I have to go serve this.
Oh well, I’ll meet her eventually.
Several days later
Sorry for the wait.
There is some stock in the back. Could you please go get it?
Understood. It is stacked up pretty high.
Yeah, I’m sorry for asking you to do it.
Oh, n-no, it’s quite all right.
Huh?
Today’s the first day I’m working with Inami-san. I wonder what kind of person she is.
Oh, are you Inami-san? Hel—
A guy!
Looks like she did it again...
Oh my.
A guy!
What the hell is this?!
K-Katanashi-kun!
Are you okay?
Senpai... Ouch... somehow.
Inami-chan.
Inami-chan, calm down.
Inami-chan!
Scary!
You’re the one that’s scary!
My, my. What’s wrong, Mahiru-chan?
Yachiyo-san! There’s a guy... there’s a guy here!
Oh, he’s just the new part-timer.
There’s a guy! It’s dangerous, Yachiyo-san!
He might have a weapon!
Mahiru-chan, you really are bad with men, aren’t you?
Weapon?!
Takanashi-kun, allow me to introduce her.
This is Inami Mahiru-chan, and she has androphobia.
Inami Mahiru
She gets scared and attacks when she sees a guy, so try not to get killed.
Try not to get killed?!
She’s very strong.
But it’s strange...
She’s a threat to your life, so Kyouko-san said she wouldn’t put you both on the same shift.
Huh? Was Inami working today?
I made a mistake.
Oh my...
Hey!
The job that I got scouted for by a small, cute senpai,
was a family restaurant filled with weird people.
I was thinking that this job wasn’t all that bad,
but I actually fear for my life
in front of the androphobic Inami-san.
What should I do?!
Can plain old me possibly survive this in the long run?
However, I don’t want to quit the job with my small and cute senpai.
You actually are a lolicon, aren’t you?
No, I’m not!
I’m not a lolicon, just a guy that likes small things... a ‘minicon’!
Item 1
Welcome to Wagnaria: Takanashi Works.
That’s just as weird, Katanashi-kun.
Next episode preview
Next episode preview:
Man, did I get in a mess.
Are you all right?
Yeah, somewhat... More importantly, just what kind of person is Inami-san?
She’s a really nice girl!
How so?!
Next time: “Inami, androphobia. That’s because I’m scared...”
Item 2
Next:
Inami, androphobia. That’s because I’m scared...
What do you mean, “you’re scared”?!
Eh? Please look forward to it!