So that’s one meat gratin.
Also the green sala–
That’s how it is, so we’ll be closed tomorrow.
Apparently, it’s going to take all day tomorrow to fix the water mains,
and we won’t have running water in the restaurant until it’s fixed.
So that means...
We’ll be closed tomorrow.
Yup.
It’s rare that we’re all off on a weekend, isn’t it?
Then that means...
What’s wrong Aoi-chan?
Yamada will be all alone here tomorrow.
Morning
Alone for breakfast.
Afternoon
Alone for lunch.
Evening
And alone for dinner.
Yamada can do whatever she wants!
Yamada...
Don’t leave the attic tomorrow.
What?
Don’t lay a finger on the restaurant’s food.
Why can’t Yamada do it when you do it all the time?
Because all the food in this place is mine!
It’s not yours.
So I have the day off tomorrow...
I’m screwed, I’m screwed, I’m screwed!
Item 8
Inami’s first time? We’re going out!
Telling her not to leave the attic at all is a bit harsh.
Yes, please comfort poor Yamada.
There, there.
Oh, I know!
If you don’t mind leaving the restaurant, why don’t we go out somewhere?
Huh?
How about going to a hot spring? We can come back by the end of the day, so it’ll be perfect.
Hot spring?
Yamada totally wants to go to a hot spring!
Hot springs feel so good.
Oh my, what’s this about hot springs?
Oh, Yachiyo-san.
Yachiyo-san, come with us to a hot spring tomorrow!
Huh? Me?
Yamada would like to go with everyone.
I’m sorry, since the restaurant will be closed
tomorrow, I need to take care of Kyouko-san.
Hot spring?
I could eat hot spring buns.
What? You’re going to go too, Kyouko-san?
I fancy eating hot spring buns.
Well, if you’re going, I’ll go as well.
Then, can you drive us, Kyouko-san?
Oh, that’s fine.
Yes!
How about we meet outside the park on 2nd Street at 8am?
Sure.
See you tomorrow.
Hot spring buns...
Good work!
Buns!
You’re coming too right, Inami-san?
What?
If we get in Kyouko-san’s car, you should be fine, right?
But even if the ride there and back is only with girls, when we arrive, there’ll be a lot of guys.
But aren’t you getting used to being
around guys, thanks to Katanashi-kun?
What? Y-You think so?
Yes! Recently, you’ve been hitting Takanashi-san less and less.
R-Really?
Well, I was actually able to hit
Takanashi-kun only three times today.
What... You’ve hit him three times today already?
Some girl friends from school have asked me before if I wanted to go, but I have always had to turn them down.
I want to go...
Th-Then let’s go together!
We’ll try our best to help when we see any guys.
Yamada will also bodyguard you!
Okay, in that case–
Inami-san.
Do you seriously think you can go to a hot spring?
What?
It’ll be all right, Katanashi-kun.
We’ll all be there, and we’ll do our best.
Your best?
Inami-san’s illness isn’t so minor that things will work out just like that.
Today, she’s hit me four times already.
W-Wait, really?
She left one out...
In addition, taking Inami-san to a hot spring on a weekend would be like unleashing a wolf on a flock of sheep.
It’s reckless!
I’m going.
I can go to a hot spring!
Even I would like to hang out with friends from time to time!
I’m... going to the hot spring.
I think... I’ll be okay!
Inami-chan!
Jeez, Katanashi-kun, you idiot!
Takanshi-san's stupid, stupid-stupid-stupid!
Oh, thanks a lot for cleaning the kitchen.
Right.
I got an invitation from Yamada-san.
It seems everyone is going to a hot spring tomorrow.
That’s right, but apparently Inami-san wants to go as well.
What was supposed to be fun trip is
quickly changing into a dangerous one.
I’m afraid so.
If you’re so worried about it, you should just go with them.
Well, since I finally have a day off, there are some things I want to take care of.
Oh.
So, even you fall behind on household chores after working for several days straight.
No, I finish my chores fine.
It’s just that tomorrow seems like a perfect day to make dried plums.
The weather’s going to be great.
I see, so Inami-san lost to dried plums.
By the way, are you going, Satou-kun?
I’m not really interested in hot springs.
Really? I don’t think you’ll get to see what Todoroki-san looks like getting out of the water all that often.
Ow! That hurts, Satou-kun!
How mean. He actually kicked me.
I doubt Inami-san has had many chances to hang out with friends because of her androphobia.
Kind of sad, isn’t it?
Oh, something like that happened?
Yeah.
You should hang out with them from time to time too.
What?
You don’t have to worry about something like that.
Besides, we have plums to dry.
Right, I’ll help too.
Sure!
I like lining up the plums.
You do help every year after all.
Something’s definitely going to happen.
As the one responsible for looking after
Inami-san, I feel bad not doing anything about it.
But the weather is perfect for drying plums.
Even I would like to hang out with friends from time to time!
Let’s see, towels and bathing suits...
Do I need them? Do I not need them?
Actually, what do you wear to go into a hot spring?
I got excited and said I’d go, but I wonder if it’ll really be all right.
But I want to have fun with everyone.
Who could be calling at this hour?
Hello?
Yamada is too excited to sleep.
Yamada is too excited about tomorrow’s hot spring trip and can’t sleep, so please chat with her.
Yamada
Store phone
Hurry up and go to sleep, Yamada.
But I’m too excited about tomorrow!
More importantly, do you really think Inami-san will be fine tomorrow?
If you’re that worried, why don’t you just come along?
Okay, I understand.
Thanks, Taneshima-san.
So... basically, you go in the hot spring naked?
What?!
Best Milk
Please, please get bigger!
I knew you’d come.
Nazuna?
Oh, good morning, Onii-chan.
I’ll dry the plums by myself today.
I’ve always helped you, so I know how to do it.
You should go out and have fun every once in a while.
Nazuna...
You’ve grown up so much.
You sure are blessed, having such an amazing sister.
Yeah, I suppose.
What about you?
Why did you decide to come?
Oh, I just came to see how you would handle things.
What will happen with Inami-san roaming free at a hot spring?
Isn’t it exciting?
Please don’t get excited over something like that.
Kyouko-san sure is late.
She definitely overslept.
What should I do? I don’t have a phone.
I’ll go get her.
Yachiyo-san, please use my cellphone.
Thank you.
Oh, Kyouko-san? It’s Yachiyo.
Where are you?
Huh? Kyouko-san?!
U-Um, how do I hang this up?
How’d it go?
Well... It seems like she was still half-asleep and hung up on me.
Then, Kyouko-san isn’t coming to get us?!
Yamada has been so excited since last night.
She can’t wait any longer. She’s at her limit!
From the sound of things, it’s pointless to try and call her back right now.
Oh no.
Taking the bus is impossible, right, Inami-chan?
Yeah, I’m sorry.
We’ve got a problem.
Satou-san!
Y-Yamada?!
Satou-san, meeting you here is a miracle.
I can only believe that fate has decreed you to take us to the hot springs.
Satou-kun, I’m sorry to ask you so
suddenly, but Kyouko-san is still sleeping.
Satou-kun, could you please take us to the hot spring?
Satou-kun, please.
Get in.
Thank you!
Yay!
Since Mahiru-chan can’t really go with you, we’ll wait here for Kyouko-san.
I’m really sorry.
But Satou-san’s going through the trouble of taking us.
B-But Kyouko-san is...
Inami-chan, do you think you could ride in Satou-san’s car?
Off we go!
Off we go...
Yeah, yeah.
Satou-kun, I’m really sorry that I had to ask this of you.
Yeah, well, I was just on my way to return a DVD anyway.
Inami-chan...
I can’t hit him; I’ve got to endure.
I know, Inami-chan!
You know how you pretend Satou-san and Souma-san are girls when you pick up the orders from the kitchen?
Y-Yeah?
Oh, I see! Satou-san is a girl.
Satou-san is a girl.
Oh, that makes things a lot better.
Now I just have to avoid looking at Satou-san until we get there!
Satou-kun, do you want some gum?
Sure, I’ll have some.
Here.
Todoroki! You!
Satou-kun?!
I’m going to hit him!
Inami-chan, endure it!
I’m out of gas.
Inami-chan, you did great!
Sorry, I forgot that I was going to get gas after returning the DVD.
My...
Satou-san, you’re useless.
That hurts.
What should we do?
It doesn’t seem like there’s a gas station near here.
What happened? What are you all doing here?
Kyouko-san! Why are you here?
When I got your call, I started
craving hot spring buns, so I hurried over.
As expected of Kyouko-san. Nice timing!
Now you’ll be all right.
Yeah, thank goodness.
Nazuna.
Your big sister got dumped again!
Where’s Souta?
He went out.
But I thought he was gonna be here to console me...
By the way, are those dried plums ready to eat yet?
Not yet, they’re still soaking right now.
Jeez... when is Souta coming back?
I’m so sad!
I wonder if Souta is at the hot spring yet?
Do you know what that is, Takanashi-kun?
What things?
Those. The ones that look like fountains.
Oh, those?
They say that if you pour water into one of those kappa, your wish will come true.
Do you have any wishes to make, Souma-san?
Anything that I want tends to happen anyway, so I don’t have any wishes.
This guy... just what is he made of?
According to yesterday’s plan, they should be getting here right around about now.
Don’t worry about it.
I bet we’ll find them real soon.
What?
See?
Jeez!
Inami-chan, calm down!
You can do it if you try!
I can’t hold back anymore!
I’m sorry!
Huh? Wait, that felt familiar somehow.
I bet it did.
Katanashi-kun!
Takanashi-kun, as I thought, you came because you were worried about Inami-san, didn’t you?
Wait, Souma-san!
Takanashi-kun...
I can’t let you cause harm by letting you loose into the wild like this.
He really is mean after all!
Sorry.
Inami-san.
This place is dangerous.
Let’s go somewhere less crowded.
H-Hey, Takanashi-kun!
As expected of Takanashi-kun.
This is great! Now that Inami-chan has
Katanashi-kun to take care of her, we won’t have to worry.
And Yamada can have Souma-san take care of her!
Y-You’re quite heavy, Yamada-san.
Souma-san, Yamada is hungry.
You’re right. It’s a little early, but let’s have lunch.
All right. Let’s go, Yachiyo.
Yes, Kyouko-san.
Souma-san, we’re leaving.
Hurry, hurry!
Takanashi-kun...
What is it?
Um...
You really are reckless.
You wanted to come, right?
I know it isn’t possible whenever there are a lot of people,
but since you’re here, just try to enjoy yourself as much as you can.
Takanashi-kun... You’re being kind of nice.
Today, I’ll watch over you for the entire walk.
Walk?
That’s how it is, so let’s go.
That was delicious!
Eating with everyone is fun.
Next, we’re eating hot spring buns.
For dessert, right?
Aoi-chan, look at that!
A statue of a kappa.
Hot spring kappa!
There sure are a lot of kappa!
Kappa, kappa...
Kappa!
You’ll trip if you get too excited!
Hot
Spring
buns
Hot spring buns are delicious.
How lovely.
What? So you left Satou-san behind?
Yeah, though Yachiyo-san did offer to stay behind with him.
No thanks.
Considering what happened last time...
If you want to know so badly, I’ll tell you.
He tried to pass it off like nothing happened, but I guess he didn’t want to be alone with the chief.
Huh?
We've wandered to a pretty desolate area.
Kappa Canyon
Wow, looks like this is the place with the Kappa Legend.
Yeah, this is my first time here.
I guess it’s about time we found something to eat.
Let’s go find a restaurant without guys.
What’s wrong? Did you hurt yourself?
N-No, it’s just that I really caused so much trouble for everyone.
I shouldn’t have come after all.
I’m...
going to go home now.
And how exactly are you going to go home?
W-Well...
Listen carefully, Inami-san.
It’s true that you’re not normal.
But that’s because of your androphobia,
not because of you.
That’s something everyone, including me, understands.
That's why Senpai tried really hard to get you to go.
Besides, look.
It’s a pretty nice view, isn’t it?
If you hadn’t come today, we
wouldn’t have been able to see this.
It’s all thanks to you.
You really tried your best today.
Let’s cure your androphobia just like this.
I’ll continue taking care of you.
Yeah.
Thank you, Takanashi-kun.
Now, we should get going.
Oh crap!
No!
You really like a rabid dog!
Ramen at a hot spring is delicious.
How great.
Souma-san.
Huh?
You look pretty worn out.
Well, looking after kids is tiring.
How’d it go with you guys?
I guess I don’t even have to ask.
I’m glad. So you were able to have a good time too, Inami-chan?
Yeah, thanks to all of you. Thank you.
I’ve got to fix my androphobia quicker so I don’t cause you guys so much trouble.
I know! In that case...
You have to try this!
Supposedly, if the water you pour into the kappa statue comes out of its mouth, your wish will come true.
I wish to become taller.
That’s just great.
But I’ve heard that it really has granted wishes before!
Me too! I heard that my friend found true love.
Really? Yay!
Then Yamada wants the ideal family.
Onii-chan!
I’m not! So stop it! Y-You’re not listening, are you?
You too, Inami-chan. Try it!
O-Okay!
I wish men weren’t so scary.
What?
Wh-Why?
So this can actually happen?
Th-This must mean that even the gods can’t help her.
There we go.
Looks like there was a leaf stuck in there.
Curry, at a hot spring? Whatever, it’s delicious.
How lovely.
I’m sorry we weren’t able to go into the water because of my curfew.
Don’t worry about it.
We dipped our feet in, and we had a lot of fun.
Let’s come here again, Inami-san.
Yeah.
Then, we’ll go home on the bus.
Right, see ya.
In the end, Satou-kun didn’t come.
I wonder if he managed to return that DVD okay.
Yachiyo, what’s wrong?
Oh, it’s nothing.
Then let’s get going!
Whew. I’m tired, but I’m glad I came.
I was able to keep Inami-san from wreaking havoc.
Huh?
Satou-kun? What’s the matter?
You guys came too?
Yeah...
Where are the others?
They just left.
I see. Oh well, get in. We’re going home.
Oh, okay.
Looks like you had some trouble getting gas,
but it’s unfortunate that you came all the way out here just to barely miss Todoroki-san.
Wha...?
I was just joking, Satou-kun.
My, my... well they were playing around all day.
Yeah.
I wonder if I’ll be able to go out with everyone again, like today.
I should be grateful for what Takanashi-kun did today, but he treated me like a rabid dog until the very end.
I honestly can’t be grateful.
Did I catch a cold?
I wonder if Nazuna was able to get everything done on her own.
Let's just get married.
Done.
I hope the dried plums turn out well.
Omoidoori nya susumanai
I can’t get as far as I’d like
Koi ni daiji na Communicate
In love, communication is most important
Donna kotoba ga meichuu
What kinds of words would hit the mark?
Kokugo jiten wo mekurou
I’ll flip through a Japanese dictionary
Omomurou ni towazugatari de atsui kimochi wo tsugemashou
Slowly and without warning, I’ll convey these passionate feelings to you
Saredo ingin na kono mune wa jouzetsu ni wa narenai
Or so I thought, as my bashful heart is nowhere near confident enough
Monooto ni Delicate desu mamoru mi no sube shirimasen
I’m delicate to sounds. I don’t even know how to protect myself
Dakedo tantou wa yaomote desu tsune ni genba shobu
But the one in charge takes the full brunt. It’s constantly a battlefield!
Kokoroiki wo takaraka ni jibun Mode de Try shiyou
I’ll louden my disposition and try again in ‘myself’ mode
Heart no Edge ni idomou
I’ll challenge at the edge of my heart
Omou dake mitsumete moshikashitara to At Random
And gaze fixedly at only my feelings. It might come anytime at random
Chance wo matte mirubeki
So it’s best to wait for your chance!
Heart no Ace wo mekurou
I’ll flip over the ace of my heart
Nenriki de mitsumete ai no katachi no Silhouette
And gaze fixedly on my willpower. I’ll search for the image
Image wo saguri dasou
Of the shape of love’s image
Nerai doori ni susumitai
I want to get to where I’m aiming for!
Neko no senaka wo mane shitai
I want to be like the back of a cat
Next episode preview
Next episode preview:
Inami-san, your father is coming to the store?
Y-Yeah. Um, and I have a favor to ask of you...
What is it?
Please become a girl!
What the hell are you saying?!
Next time, “Kotori-chan appears!!”
Next: Item 9
Kotori-chan appears!!
So, can you?
Shut up.