Kazue
Hey! I'm studying right now, so don't bother me.
Izumi
I'm back!
Kozue
Oh! Kozue-oneechan, welcome back!
Welcome back.
What's that?
Sou-chan, you always get hand-me-downs, so I bought you a brand new stuffed animal.
Souta
Thanks, Kozue-oneechan!
Nazuna
Look, look.
It's Rabbit-san!
Don't just sit there watching that!
Item 6
Souta's melancholy, the girls of the Takanashi family.
Souta, you used to be so cute back then.
It'd be a problem if I were still like that!
Jeez, throw that stuff away already.
How can you say that?
Our late father shot that video.
It's like a memento for me,
even though we don't actually see him in it.
There sure are a lot of videos of you, Onii-chan.
That's probably because you were cute, being his eldest son.
Then it would have been nice if he had at least dressed me like a son.
It would have been better if you had just grown up as a girl.
What are you saying?
Well, because I don't have any material for a romance novel.
Do you have writer's block again?
Our family is mostly female.
Kozue-chan constantly changes her boyfriends,
Nazuna-chan is in elementary school,
and Kazue-neesan is divorced.
As if you're in a position to say anything!
It's funny to think that, even with so many girls in the family, there's no material for a romance novel.
But speaking of a lot of girls,
this place has a lot too.
Thanks for February.
Since Souma's off today, this is from the two of us.
Oh my!
March 14th
I'm so happy! Thank you very much.
Is it food?
Wrong.
It's a shame you won't be able to give this to the manager.
I-I didn't mean it like that.
I already have Kyouko-san's ready.
You previously gave her chocolate on Valentine's Day, even though she's a girl.
That's because she's cooler than any guy.
Then you should be getting some in return today.
Don't be silly Satou-kun, Kyouko-san's a girl.
Japanese just isn't getting through to her.
Satou-san: things seem to be as difficult as always for him.
Finding it
hard to
enter the
break room
Senpai!
What is it?
Thank you for last month.
This is for you.
Oh my!
You didn't have to do that.
I'm sorry I put you through all that trouble.
Senpai, you sound like an old lady.
I'm not an old lady!
Oh, I'm sorry.
You're still a child... small and cute.
I'm not a child! Stop making fun of me!
She's so cute.
What? A return gift?
Yes.
Thank you very much, Inami-san. This is for you.
S-Sorry for the trouble.
Wait, what are you doing? You can't hand it to me from over there!
Well, I don't want to get hit.
A-Are you going to throw it to me?
No. That would be too rude, so...
3,980 Yen
(tax included)
A workman's magic hand
I bought it through mail order.
Here, personal delivery.
Thank you for doing this for me...
Is that what I should be saying?
Oh, hairpins.
This many?
Yeah. I heard you change them a lot, so I thought this would be a good idea.
S-Something like this...
I'm sorry. You don't like them?
I don't know if I should use something like this or...
set them aside carefully!
Wh-Whatever you like.
I'm sorry for overreacting.
I've just never received a gift like this before.
Um, please don't make such a big deal out of it.
I'll accept them with thanks for now, and then use them later!
To be honest, it embarrasses me to see her enjoy the gift so much.
Magic Hand
Takanashi
I'm back!
Drunk again.
Kozue-neesan, don't sleep in the hall.
Oh my, Souta sneaking into someone else's room without permission.
Night crawling?
Please die.
Souta, your sister got dumped again.
Jeez, is that any excuse for not going to sleep in your own room?
I can't go on without sake.
Sou-chan...
Izumi-neesan.
I'm sorry, Kozue-chan, I wanted to do something,
but my arms start to ache when I carry anything...
heavier than a pen.
Furthermore, it doesn't hurt until three days later.
Souta, your sister is so sad.
Yeah, well, I wasn't really expecting anything like that from you, Izumi-neesan.
Your deadline's almost here, isn't it?
You should back to your room and finish up your draft.
Souta, don't spoil Izumi so much.
Kazue-neesan.
Hey, Izumi, get off the floor.
But...
I feel weary when I stand up.
Stand up!
Sou-chan, help me.
I'm weaker than usual right before my deadlines.
Souta, give me some more alcohol, alcohol.
Try to get along.
It's not like I enjoy fighting. I just...
Kazue-neesan is scowling at me.
I'm just looking!
But your eyes are scary.
You rarely stand up, so it just seems like I'm scowling at you.
And you're taller than me!
Seriously...
how long do you plan on being a writer?
You whine about work all year.
You don't seem to be enjoying it much, either.
You also always wear black, so you're always depressing those around you.
When I look at you...
Argh! I just get so irritated!
Souta, this is your problem too!
You should be making her clean her own room!
But she said she doesn't have the strength to.
I'm not very good at cleaning, and I don't have time for it because of the book.
If you're feeling down all the time and can't even take care of yourself, the work doesn't suit you.
It's not too late.
Quit now.
Did I say something wrong?
That was your fault, Kazue-neesan.
Well, you two are like apples and oranges.
Oh, welcome home, Mahiru.
I-I'm back.
Oh? What's that?
U-Um, this is...
A return gift for White Day?
Yeah, I received a lot.
Well, well, isn't that great? Oh, they're cute.
Wh-What should I do with them?
Wear them, of course.
But if I started wearing them all of a sudden, wouldn't it look like I was too excited about them?
That's not true.
It'd be terrible if I lost them too.
B-But since they are very cute...
A-Anyway, I'm going to go put them away somewhere safe!
She seems so happy.
That's enough, come out already!
I'm coming in.
Wh-What is this?
You told me I should do things for myself, so when I tried cleaning my room...
it got even messier.
Izumi, remind me again, how old are you?
28. Why?
No reason, just felt like asking.
Is this girl all right?
Enough already.
Forget what I said earlier.
I was wrong.
Kazue-neesan.
Anyway, don't worry yourself so much.
Remember to take a break or do something else every now and then.
But work...
Try watching TV, getting out of the house, or engaging in conversation with others.
You might find material for your book in some unexpected places.
Then, I wonder if I could use your hopeless, despondent period leading up to your divorce as material for a love story?
BANG
You got mad?
Of course!
You little...
Get along.
I wonder what's wrong. Takanashi-kun seems down.
I'm flat broke. What should I do?
Oh right! Even though he's a responsible boy, he's still a high schooler.
There must be a lot of things he wants, and I guess the part-time pay isn't enough.
This month is going to be tough.
Family expenses...
Family expenses?!
Takanashi
Just as I thought, we're not going to have enough this month.
We don't have anything left, and there are still five days left until the end of the month.
What are we going to do?
You're irresponsible.
You don't have anything left because you waste money.
Be more responsible.
It's because you spend all our living expenses on alcohol!
But that's because I kept getting dumped this month!
Plus, I've already spent my paycheck.
Right, of course.
Even if I asked Kazue-neesan, there's probably no way she'd give me more than her share for the month.
And since Izumi-neesan has shut herself up in her room because of her deadlines...
I guess I have no other choice.
I'll have to take some money out of my personal savings.
Onii-chan.
Hm?
If you need money, I have some.
What?
Here.
Wh-Where did you get this?!
Kazue-oneechan gave it to me when I asked her.
What a scary child!
Sorry for the trouble, Nazuna.
Oh yeah, and about Kozue-neechan's drinking problem...
She'll happily drink any kind of alcohol, so it'd be more cost-effective to stock up on the cheap stuff.
I'm already in sixth grade.
I grew up really fast for you, Onii-chan.
It's really true, almost enough to make me cry.
So please rely on me more.
Nazuna... for my sake...
I'm at the point where I can manipulate anyone in the family.
At this rate, my little sister will turn out to be an exquisitly devilish woman because of me.
Anyway, I'll just try not to think about it.
Souta.
Where are you going?
Just grocery shopping.
Oh, then please buy me some sake!
Buy it yourself.
Why?!
You're that wasted and you still want to drink more?!
But I can't function without alcohol!
Jeez...
Sou-chan.
Izumi-neesan?
Could you...
It can wait until after dinner,
but can you help me clean my room?
Oh, sure.
Sorry.
What the hell?!
You're only nice to Izumi-nee!
Souta, you jerk!
What's with her?
Jeez, she's even more drunk than usual.
Sou-chan, please forgive her.
She's a very lonely person.
So please take care of her as much as the rest of us.
Take care of you? I'm not your mother.
Stupid Souta! What's with that guy?
I'm going to make him hate me!
I'm going to mess up all of his small, cute...
I thought it'd be full of cute things, but it's a pretty normal room.
This is... the bunny I bought for him ages ago.
Is this the only cute thing in his room?
If this is his only decoration...
could it be that Souta...
actually loves me a lot?
I love you, Kozue-oneechan!
If only Kozue-neesan weren't drunk all the time...
What should I do?
Mahiru, please go buy groceries.
We're having curry tonight, but we've run out of rice.
I told her that I couldn't because too many people around at this time.
I really can't do it.
I'd end up punching all the guys in there.
Inami-san.
What are you doing here?
U-Um... well...
I-Inami-san!
I-It's nothing! I was just trying to go to the store!
Please calm down!
At this rate there will be casualties.
In any case, I'm glad I found you before you went into a busy area.
I'm sorry you ended up having to buy it for me.
No problem. I was going there anyway.
Also, I know it's a little late to say this, but I'm impressed that you can actually walk to school.
Ah. Well, if I leave really early in the morning, I don't meet anyone...
And if I'm going to the restaurant, I know a pretty deserted route.
And on the way back, I take the dark, deserted roads, so I'm fine.
A spy?
Shall we head home then?
I'll walk you halfway.
What?
Y-You don't have to do that.
I can't just leave you here.
It would be a problem if you attacked some pedestrians.
I'm really all right.
I-I'm going to end up following you from quite far behind anyway.
Then should we hold hands?
Here. It's a good thing I brought this.
To think she'd actually hold it...
Souta.
Kazue-neesan, going home?
Yeah.
Who's this?
She's a coworker.
I bumped into her at the grocery store, so I'm walking her home.
That's great but...
What sort of relationship do you have with her?
Huh? I just told you.
Does your workplace have some sort of strange skinship?
G-Good evening. I'm Inami Mahiru.
Oh, hello. You're so polite!
Nice to meet you.
I'm Souta's older sister, Kazue.
Thank you for always taking care of him.
Takanashi-kun's sister is so big.
His sister from before was big too.
It makes me kind of nervous.
L-Likewise. Thank you for letting me abuse him.
Abuse?
Oh, I'm sorry! That came out wrong!
I meant to say that he's always taking care of me.
I... I don't really abuse him.
I'm sorry, I do abuse him!
Inami-san, please be quiet.
Souta, come here.
What's going on?
Abuse? Exactly what kind of relationship do you have with her?
What? You've got it all wrong.
It's true she abuses me, but that's just her personality.
I didn't give you permission to work so you could have an impure relationship!
What? She seems to be getting the wrong idea.
Like I said, you've got it all wrong.
She can't help but hit guys because of her androphobia.
Oh, so that's what you meant by abuse.
Then it's fine.
"Then it's fine?"
If that's the case, then hit him as much as you like.
He's very durable.
Seems like he has it tough at home too.
I'm sorry, Takanashi-kun.
Oh, my house is close by, so here is fine.
I see.
Be careful.
Yes, thank you very much.
Oh, that's right.
Would you like an apple?
They were cheap, so I bought quite a few of them.
Th-Thank you.
Then I'll see you at work.
Souta!
I'm sorry, Souta.
It looks like Nee-san had it wrong.
Truce.
A-Are you okay, Kozue-neesan?
Did you drink too much?
Is this some strange illness?
If you're feeling sick, you should go to the hospital.
Welcome back, Onii-chan.
Oh, Kazue-oneesan, you were with him too.
Yeah, I just happened to bump into him.
Oh, a value-for-money three-pack of sake.
Way to go onii-chan!
Oh, manuscript paper and ink.
I was just about to go buy some.
Good for you, Izumi-oneechan.
I love you too, Souta.
You're really acting weird, Kozue-neesan.
Souta!
Hurry up and start dinner.
There's nothing to be embarrassed about!
Thanks for the manuscript paper, Sou-chan.
That's not it–
But I love you!
Um, Mahiru...
Yeah, mom?
Well...
Oh, it's nothing.
Dinner's almost ready.
Omoidoori nya susumanai
I can’t get as far as I’d like
Koi ni daiji na Communicate
In love, communication is most important
Donna kotoba ga meichuu
What kinds of words would hit the mark?
Kokugo jiten wo mekurou
I’ll flip through a Japanese dictionary
Omomurou ni towazugatari de atsui kimochi wo tsugemashou
Slowly and without warning, I’ll convey these passionate feelings to you
Saredo ingin na kono mune wa jouzetsu ni wa narenai
Or so I thought, as my bashful heart is nowhere near confident enough
Monooto ni Delicate desu mamoru mi no sube shirimasen
I’m delicate to sounds. I don’t even know how to protect myself
Dakedo tantou wa yaomote desu tsune ni genba shobu
But the one in charge takes the full brunt. It’s constantly a battlefield!
Kokoroiki wo takaraka ni jibun Mode de Try shiyou
I’ll louden my disposition and try again in ‘myself’ mode
Heart no Edge ni idomou
I’ll challenge at the edge of my heart
Omou dake mitsumete moshikashitara to At Random
And gaze fixedly at only my feelings. It might come anytime at random
Chance wo matte mirubeki
So it’s best to wait for your chance!
Heart no Ace wo mekurou
I’ll flip over the ace of my heart
Nenriki de mitsumete ai no katachi no Silhouette
And gaze fixedly on my willpower. I’ll search for the image
Image wo saguri dasou
Of the shape of love’s image
Nerai doori ni susumitai
I want to get to where I’m aiming for!
Neko no senaka wo mane shitai
I want to be like the back of a cat
Jeez! Don't break my door, Kozue-neesan.
Onii-chan, your room doesn't really have a lot of cute things, does it?
Oh, ever since I was little and let my favorite stuffed rabbit get dirty and worn out,
I've been careful to put the rest of them away.
Oh, is that right?
Here, is this dictionary all right?
Yep. Thanks, Onii-chan.
This little bunny is still holding down the fort though, isn't it?
Yeah, because it was my favorite.
Next episode preview
Next episode preview:
Senpai, we have a problem!
What's wrong, Katanashi-kun?
Otoo-san is coming back!
Oh, that's all?
Oh, and this time the "souvenir" seems to be a girl.
What?! A girl?!
Next time, "Otoo, whom we haven't seen for a while, and a new worker = Yamada(!?)"
Next: Item 7
Otoo-san, whom we haven't seen for a
while, and a new worker = Yamada(!?)
Another thing to worry about.