Otoo is coming back today.
Or rather, the edible souvenirs are coming.
Yay, Otoo-san!
It might not be sweets, you know.
I’m going to knock you out if you say such stupid things.
We’ve had things like masks before too.
Huh?
There’s still a possibility that he’ll bring something el—
Oh, hey.
Um, who’s this?
Trainee
Wh-Who is that?
Item 7
Otoo-san, whom we haven’t seen for a while, and a new worker = Yamada(!?)
I don’t know—new hire?
But doesn’t Kyouko-san decide those things?
Kyouko-san, do you know?
That’s...
not edible!
Inami-san, please go throw the manager somewhere so she won’t be a bother.
Eh?
Otoo-san, you always bring back a variety of things while you’re out looking for your missing wife,
but did you actually snatch a girl that looks like her this time?
That’s k-kidnapping.
You can’t do something like that, Otoo-san!
You’ve got it wrong!
A-Anyway, please introduce yourself.
Okay.
I’m Yamada Aoi.
Um... Uh, how old are you?
What? Me? I’m 16.
Then, I’m 16 too.
“Then”?! How suspicious.
So, what’s her story?
U-Um, I was looking for my wife as always,
and was at a train station.
I thought it was dangerous for a girl to be out alone at night and that she might be lost, so I called out to her.
I am poor and have been living modestly, but recently my house burned down, scattering my family, I barely made it out alive.
Just afterward I fell and hit my head, losing my memory, so I can’t find my family or home and have nowhere to return to.
Becoming alone at such a young age. Isn’t it amazing?
Yes, it sounds like an amazing lie.
A lie?
Yes, her story is inconsistent and vague.
She’s very suspicious.
Could it be that you just ran away from home and with nowhere to stay
you decided to take advantage of
Otoo-san because he seemed kind?
Y-You’re wrong.
She’s so easy to read.
What’s wrong? Are you all right?
Katanashi-kun, you shouldn’t call girls liars.
That’s right. I feel bad for her.
Just look at how she’s shaking.
I suppose there might be a chance she has a serious reason for this.
Um, excuse me, I was just kidding there.
It must have been difficult for you—losing all your belongings in that fire.
Oh, no.
I brought everything I need.
Is she even trying to keep it secret?
Well, that’s the story.
I’d like to let her stay here, Manager Shirafuji.
I won’t accept anything you bring that isn’t food.
Kyouko-san!
The poor girl...
Um...
Shut up. Go home.
High-grade cake box
Hired.
Otoo, she has a lot of potential.
I see. That’s great.
Good thing I brought out the sweets like Otoo-san told me to do.
A new hire! Nice to meet you, Aoi-chan!
I’m Taneshima Poplar. This is Inami-chan.
N-Nice to meet you.
I know it’s been tough on you with the fire and memory loss,
but here you can think of us as older sisters, okay?
We’re both 17.
Senpai totally believed her.
Onee-san...
I’m inexperienced and rather nervous after all that’s happened, so I’ll be in your care.
Senpai, she’s already making light of you.
So small.
So, Takanashi, you take care of her.
What?!
That guy seems seems kind of sharp; he’ll be troublesome.
You just thought that I was troublesome, didn’t you?
No I didn’t.
Well then...
For the time being, I won’t just tell
you to go home as soon as possible.
Pleased to meet you, Yamada-san.
Yamada-san?
Oh, right. I’m Yamada.
It’s a fake name?
Well, let’s put her to work.
Yes.
Again...?
Yamada-san, make sure you write that down in the damage report.
Yamada-san.
Yamada-san!
Hey, Yamada-san!
Yamada—
Person using Yamada as an alias.
It’s not an alias.
Right, right.
Takanashi-san, I can’t respond to the name Yamada.
Then tell me your real name.
Please just call me by my first name, Aoi.
So her first name is real, huh?
I’d really rather not.
Calling a coworker by their first name is...
Don’t worry; I won’t think,
“Four-eyes is getting overly familiar with me.”
I’m just going to call you Yamada!
Okay, Yamada-san, I’ll teach you how to restock. Give it a try on your own.
First, open this.
Still, what’s with this girl?
She speaks well and has a dignified aura about her.
It’s like she’s some high-class young lady, but...
Yamada-san, we have a can opener.
Yamada-san. Yamada!
I didn’t know how to open it.
If you didn’t know, just ask. Are you a barbarian?
But you said to do it by myself.
I wanted to see if you could do it by yourself.
If there’s something you can’t do, then please ask.
Unreasonable.
Also, your face is really showing your mean streak.
I hear that all the time.
How is it going, Yamada-san? Are you working hard?
Yes, it’s going perfectly.
Don’t lie!
I see. How admirable.
Please call me Aoi.
O-Okay.
A-Anyway, do your best, okay?
I’ve decided. I’ve decided on Otoo-san.
Otoo Aoi. It has a nice ring to it.
Otoo-san has a wife.
He has a wife?
That’s still fine. Actually, that’s even better.
Wait!
I’ll be their adopted child.
An ideal father, and even comes a mother as well.
Again, wait!
If you want a family, why not go back home?
Back home...?
What... are you talking about?
Seems like there’s a new hire on the floor, Satou-kun.
Yeah, “Yamada,” was it?
I heard Otoo-san randomly picked her up.
If she works properly, I don’t care about that.
You’re right.
But why did things got busier now that we have more hands?
Yamada-san!
Seems like Yamada-san is the reason.
A few days later
Well now, I wonder if something interesting will happen today.
What’s wrong, Satou-kun?
Oh right, Yamada-san is living in the restaurant.
Bring me Yamada.
I like natto.
I see. Go clean it out immediately.
But soy beans are good for your health.
Clean it out.
Now, now, Satou-kun. Who cares about a little natto?
The bigger issue might be that she uses the kitchen stoves without permission,
and the store’s cups, plates, and garbage bags for personal use,
and carries the customer chairs into the attic.
I’m against violence.
I feel bad for her if you get that angry, Satou-kun.
Todoroki.
Yachiyo-san!
Since you live here, it’s understandable that you need to use the refrigerator.
But we do use it for work, so make sure to keep your stuff in the back, okay?
Okay.
You can use restaurant’s stuff,
but always be sure to get permission first.
’Kay, ’kay.
Aoi-chan is so cute, isn’t she?
She’s not cute at all.
Seems like Todoroki-san has taken a real shine to Yamada-san.
I can’t really deal with her. There’s just something...
You remind me...
Food, food...
...a bit of Kyouko-san.
Something about the eyes.
Oh, so that’s why she pisses me off.
Yachiyo-san is so great.
Last time, it was Otoo-san.
Otoo-san is the father. Yachiyo-san is the mother.
Oh, really?
Yamada does not have a family at the moment, so she is currently recruiting.
Yamada-san...
Excited
And once I find them, it’ll be like an afternoon soap opera—full of love and hate!
What are you going to do with that?
Yes, Yamada has decided.
Yachiyo, how’s Yamada?
Yes, she still can’t do any of her work properly yet, but she’s so cute.
Cute?
She’s cute.
Right, Otoo-san?
Right, yeah.
I guess it’s probably because I didn’t bring food this time, but Todoroki-san is in high spirits.
But on the contrary, the manager seems to be in a bad mood.
Yachiyo-san!
Oh, what is it, Aoi-chan?
What is she up to?
Please be Yamada’s mother.
Mother?
Yes. Otoo-san will be the father, so please marry him.
And then, make trouble for Otoo-san’s first wife.
You’re already making making trouble right now, Yamada!
This time, I was happy that instead of having Kyouko-san taken away from me by Otoo-san’s souvenirs, we got a new hire.
But now the topic has suddenly changed to marriage between myself and Otoo-san...
Why must you always disrupt the peace days Kyouko-san and I have together,
Otoo-san?
I knew it. She still found a reason to draw her blade on me!
Hey, Yamada,
I’m not sure what’s going on, but Yachiyo is mine.
I won’t give you Otoo either.
Yachiyo is mine.
Is mine.
Is mine...
I’m sorry, Aoi-chan. I belong to Kyouko-san.
Yachiyo, parfait please.
Yes, Kyouko-san!
Are you all right, Otoo-san?
Yeah, I’ve gotten used to it.
So Yachiyo-san is that scary when she’s mad.
Yamada-san...
She’s getting more and more like my ideal mother!
What are you looking for in a family?
Otoo-san left me.
Oh, yeah...
Finding his wife seems to be his highest priority.
Aoi-chan looks so depressed.
It’s like she’s in mourning.
Yamada!
Otoo-san is still alive!
Yamada, you cut corners when you were cleaning the break room, didn’t you? Souma-san told me.
Yamada, you’ve been swiping a little of the store’s seasonings each day, haven’t you? Souma told me.
I’m sorry, Yamada-san. They’re making me report all of your misdeeds to them.
But I’ll keep quiet about that order you just messed up.
Yamada...
Souma-san is terrible.
There wouldn’t be a problem if you just did things right.
How does he know everyone’s weaknesses?
Just who is this Souma-san?
Who knows.
If I could get some dirt on Souma-san, he’d be nicer to me.
Then I could do anything I want.
Work seriously.
Souma-san?
I always hit him right away, so I
haven’t really talked to him before.
Um, you see...
he knows an awful lot,
he’s very knowledgeable, and he knows a lot of...
I work with him, yet I don’t know
anything about him. I’m a terrible person.
I’m a terrible person.
Taneshima-san.
About Souma-kun?
Now that you mention it, I don’t know anything about him.
All he really talks about are other people.
Oh, his personality isn’t so great.
I kind of knew that already.
How could you say such a thing, Satou-kun?
Then, do you know something about him?
I know everything about Kyouko-san.
Do you want to hear?
Yamada, it’s going to get lengthy from here, so escape while you can.
Yamada-san, I hear you’re investigating me. Have you learned anything?
I couldn’t learn anything.
I see. How unfortunate.
So sorrowful.
Wait, what? Why are you crying?
It’s just that nobody knows anything about you.
Satou-san is even saying that you have a terrible personality.
Wha—?! So cruel.
Um, I just don’t like talking about myself.
Everyone in this restaurant is close to each other, but you have no friends.
So sorrowful!
A-Anyway, please stop crying. If anybody saw us right now...
Souma-san is making Aoi-chan cry.
So those are your true colors!
Taneshima-san!
I’m defeated.
For the first time in my life, someone has dirt on me.
Even Taneshima-san ran away from you. So sorrowful, Souma-san.
Yamada will do anything the sorrowful Souma-san asks of her.
Could you please stop saying “sorrowful”?
So Soumarrowful-san.
Please don’t connect it like that.
Please think of Yamada as your younger sister and confide in her as such.
W-Well, that’s a little—
Please...
Okay, please tell me anything!
Time for work, time for work.
What did you use to blackmail her?
No, it’s more like the opposite.
And then, Kyouko-san said that the parfait I made for her was so good.
I was so happy.
And then, are you listening, Satou-kun?
Are you all right?
Oh, Satou-san is listening to the chief prattle on again.
It’s amazing that he can endure it every day.
You’re naive, Takanashi-kun!
He suddenly got energetic.
A girl looks her best when she’s
speaking about someone she loves.
At Her Most Beautiful
Oh, happiness accompanied by misery...
How wretched.
All right, now to work.
Yachiyo-san!
Oh, Aoi-chan, what is it?
What were you speaking to Satou-san about?
We weren’t really talking so much as just him kindly listening to me talk about...
Is that all right?
You’re right, I was being selfish going on and on,
even though Satou-san has someone he likes, too.
But Satou-san likes you, Yachiyo-san.
What?
Yamada doesn’t like Satou-san, but she feels bad for him.
What? There’s no way.
It’s quite obvious. It’s clear he treats you the nicest, he
doesn’t snap back at you, and he doesn’t get mad at you.
Yamada! She’s lousy at her work, but she’s really sharp with these things!
You’re the one who Satou-san likes.
All right, Yamada-san, come here a sec.
You can’t say those kinds of things.
If you just blurt out everything you know or find out, you will mess up your relations with other people.
Reflect on what you’ve done.
Geez, this has become very interesting.
Don’t praise her!
What is it this time? I won’t make food for the manager.
No, um...
You don’t look well, Todoroki.
Are you sick or som—
Ah!
Painfully hurt
Sorry.
S-Sorry.
Um, about the person you like...
This again?
Aoi-chan said...
that it was me.
Um, I know she’s wrong, but I wanted to make sure.
There’s no way, right?
It’s impossible, right? Right?
He broke?!
Will you cut it out already?
If you want to know so badly, I’ll tell you.
Nobody’s there.
Don’t talk.
Don’t look back.
That’s how things are.
Running away?!
You did it, Satou-kun! Now maybe Todoroki-san will be a little more...
S-Satou-san?
I’m going home.
Wait, Satou-kun?! We still have work to do!
Satou-kun?! Am I supposed to do it by myself?! Hey! Hey!
The next day
Oh, Manager.
What?
A while back, you said not to form a
relationship with a coworker here, right?
What’s this, all of a sudden?
No, it’s just...
Regardless of how serious one is about it, nothing good ever comes from workplace romances.
Especially when it’s one-sided, or when a love triangle forms. The restaurant stops functioning right and everything goes bad.
Well, it’s probably got nothing to do with us.
I wonder.
Satou-kun likes me...
All this time,
I didn’t realize it and just gushed about Kyouko-san.
Hey, you all right, Yachiyo?
Kyouko-san.
Have one of these.
Yachiyo will now commit seppuku.
Please assist me.
Hey, calm down.
Oh, Senpai, excuse me, I didn’t see you.
midget
This is unusually cruel.
Satou-san! It was Satou-san!
Satou-san!
Satou-kun, your hand! Run it under cold water!
He’s taking it pretty hard. Even without hearing her reply.
Well, it’s pretty obvious what her reply is going to be.
Anyway, with the hardest workers from the floor and kitchen acting like this, the restaurant is going to collapse.
Are Satou-san and Yachiyo-san fighting?
Hm?
All right, I’ll leave the rest to you.
He passed the buck?
Fighting won’t solve anything!
Talk it over and make up!
It didn’t work.
You did a great job getting them to sit together.
Please go back to your work, Senpai.
Todoroki.
Y-Yes?!
I...
I can see...
a ghost behind you.
Satou-san broke!
Even Todoroki-san is disturbed!
A ghost?
Yes, that ghost sticks to just one person all the time.
Even though the ghost thinks it’s happy,
but I think that perhaps looking at the outside world and yearning to experience new things might be better for...
Is he trying to make things vague before he gets rejected?
Actually, that description fits her perfectly.
That’s why I’ve kept kept quiet up till now.
Inner feeling
What should I do
if she thinks
I'm an idiot
What should I do
if she thinks
I'm an idiot
What should I do
if she thinks
I'm an idiot
What should I do if she thinks I’m an idiot?
Is that what it was?
Her cluelessness has always irritated me, but right now...
I’m so glad she’s like that.
I’m sorry. Not only was I clueless, I  misunderstood things because I thought too much of myself.
That’s all it was, so go on back to work.
Give my regards to Taneshima.
You’re so nice, Satou-kun.
Out of all the boys, I like you the most.
Are you all right?
Yeah.
I’ll head back to work then.
Aren’t you glad that you’re number one out of all the guys?
I-I guess everything turned out all right, Satou-san.
Please work as hard as always, okay?
Yeah.
But I’m going home for today.
Th-Thank you for your hard work!
S-Satou-kun, again?! Wait a second!
Satou-kun! Satou-kun!
Huh? What’s wrong?
Were you guys doing something fun while Yamada was away?
It wasn’t fun!
That’s not fair. Please include Yamada as well!
This is all your fault to begin with—
Wait, what’s that you’re holding?
Th-This is t-trash.
Yamada didn’t break them.
Yamada!
Omoidoori nya susumanai
I can’t get as far as I’d like
Koi ni daiji na Communicate
In love, communication is most important
Donna kotoba ga meichuu
What kinds of words would hit the mark?
Kokugo jiten wo mekurou
I’ll flip through a Japanese dictionary
Omomurou ni towazugatari de atsui kimochi wo tsugemashou
Slowly and without warning, I’ll convey these passionate feelings to you
Saredo ingin na kono mune wa jouzetsu ni wa narenai
Or so I thought, as my bashful heart is nowhere near confident enough
Monooto ni Delicate desu mamoru mi no sube shirimasen
I’m delicate to sounds. I don’t even know how to protect myself
Dakedo tantou wa yaomote desu tsune ni genba shobu
But the one in charge takes the full brunt. It’s constantly a battlefield!
Kokoroiki wo takaraka ni jibun Mode de Try shiyou
I’ll louden my disposition and try again in ‘myself’ mode
Heart no Edge ni idomou
I’ll challenge at the edge of my heart
Omou dake mitsumete moshikashitara to At Random
And gaze fixedly at only my feelings. It might come anytime at random
Chance wo matte mirubeki
So it’s best to wait for your chance!
Heart no Ace wo mekurou
I’ll flip over the ace of my heart
Nenriki de mitsumete ai no katachi no Silhouette
And gaze fixedly on my willpower. I’ll search for the image
Image wo saguri dasou
Of the shape of love’s image
Nerai doori ni susumitai
I want to get to where I’m aiming for!
Neko no senaka wo mane shitai
I want to be like the back of a cat
I’m so glad that we made up, Satou-kun.
This was the first time I’ve ever felt
so awkward around someone that I felt ill.
Stomach medicine.
And then I had to think about so many
things that it really made my head hurt.
Headache medicine.
Satou-kun, you’re such a nice guy!
Take those with water.
Satou-san...
Always so well prepared.
Next episode preview
Next episode preview:
Hot springs!
Hot springs?
Katanashi-kun, do you want to go with us?
What’s this all of a sudden, Senpai?
I’m going with Inami-chan and the others, so I wondered if you wanted to come along.
With Inami-san?
Next time, “Inami’s first time? We’re going out!”
Next: Item 8
Inami’s first time? We’re going out!
I hope nobody gets injured.
What?