Hello, I'm Kotori-chan.
What are you doing, Yamada-san?
Now that I think about it, Takanashi-kun's cross-dressing was really something.
It was a standard he could be proud of,
but he really seemed to hate doing it.
I wonder why.
Yeah; I wonder why.
Well, in this case, he only did it for Inami-san's sake.
But he ended up yelling at Inami-san's father in a very manly way.
Do you think it made her father suspect that he was cross-dressing?
Nah; I think it was fine.
In the end, her father realized his mistakes and apologized.
Even though Takanashi-kun
cross-dressed, he still showed a manly side.
And towards the end it seemed like Inami-san didn't even care about her father.
Kotori-chan sure left a destructive wake in many places.
And that's what happened last time.
Anyway, just don't create too much trouble.
I'll be leaving on a business trip today.
Item 10
A suspicious situation... Nazuna works.
"I apologize for all the inconvenience I've caused at the restaurant."
"From now on, I plan to repent every day and I will work hard to regain your confidence in me."
"Love, Dad."
And so, my dad sent me this letter of apology and has allowed me to continue working here.
I-It's all thanks to Takanashi-kun.
Thank you very much.
Inami-san, you're too far away.
I thought we were able to talk to each other at close range lately.
Have I done anything strange?
It's not that you did something strange.
It's because you cross-dressed that one time.
Because I cross-dressed...?
She's treating me like a pervert?
Th-That's not how I meant it!
Because you worked so hard for Inami-chan...
Um... so...
She doesn't see you as just another guy anymore.
So she thinks I'm a transvestite?!
Noo... that's not it!
This is unbelievable!
What is it?
If there's something you want to say, just say it!
Uh... This and that are...
Yes?
This and that are...
totally unrelated!
Which and what are?!
This is why I didn't want to do it!
I'm so sorry!
Inami-chan!
She hit me.
So this means that...
she still sees me as a normal guy.
I'm so glad.
What's wrong, Takanashi?
Did something finally awaken in you?
Inami-chan...
Taneshima-san... What should I do?
You fell for Katanashi-kun, right?
Y-Yeah.
Then, you shouldn't hit him.
But...
Even still, I still get the urge to hit guys!
I like him, but I hate him.
What should I do?
What's with this?!
Inami-chan...
Now I've just got yet another reason why I can't stay here.
So you were keeping your distance so you wouldn't hit him.
Huh? Wait.
I'm always thinking about Takanashi-kun, day and night.
But weren't you saying that before too?
Hitting him because you were too close.
Always thinking about Katanashi-kun, day and night.
That's right! Nothing has changed.
Huh?
Now that I think about it, it was like this even when I didn't like him.
If things haven't changed, you should just act like you always have.
W-Wait just a minute...
So this means that...
From the very beginning, I've always l-liked...
They say there's a thin line between love and hate.
Don't think about it too hard.
Th-That's right!
Right.
This place is going to fall apart.
I did it again.
So you were keeping your distance because you were grateful and didn't want to hit me?
S-Something like that.
You don't have to worry about that.
Just act the same as you always have, and try to hit me without actually killing me.
That's hard.
I'll be with you until you're cured.
Be with me?!
Inami-san, you're boiling.
Five more days until Kyouko-san returns from her business trip.
The chief sure is depressed when the manager isn't around.
What are you doing, Yamada?
I'm not Yamada.
I'm a customer.
I've finished my shift, so I've come here to eat.
ding dong
Excuse me, Miss. You only need to press the bell once.
I know.
Oh, so you're doing it to harrass me.
Actually, it's depressing eating alone.
So?
Please stay here while I eat.
Look, if you don't want to eat alone that badly, eat out back.
But Yamada is a customer.
What are you looking at?
A cute picture.
Let me see!
Sure, here.
So cute.
Oh, Yamada still hasn't seen it!
Be gone! Be gone! Be gone!
Stop littering the place.
Disintegrate! Disintegrate! Disintegrate!
Takanashi-kun, the data is all on my computer.
What is this?! Is this harrassment?!
No, I didn't plan on printing it out, but someone asked me to.
Who?!
Souma-san!
Here.
Thank you!
No problem.
Isn't this one great, Aoi-chan?
Just as I thought, you have great taste, Taneshima-san.
Ever since then, it seems like Taneshima-san has been obsessed with the cross-dressing Takanashi-kun.
Recovered them somehow
Souma-san is one thing, but now even Senpai...
I'm sorry. This is all because I asked you to cross-dress.
Inami-san.
It's all my fault, right?
Yes, it's all your androphobia's fault.
It's painful when he says it so bluntly.
And so, Inami-san...
Hm?
In order to cure your androphobia, let's get even closer than we were before.
What?
Anyway, let's just go home together from now on.
Primary objective: Go somewhere with me while holding hands.
Wouldn't that be considered... a date?!
Wh-Why... Ow...
I-I only beat you up just now to... hide my embarrassment!
I don't care anymore...
Kyouko-san...
Yachiyo-san really is terribly depressed because Kyouko-san is away on her business trip.
Poor Yachiyo-san.
Yamada will go cheer her up!
Good luck, Aoi-chan!
Yachiyo-san.
I'm the manager.
Yamada
Kyouko-san.
She got even more depressed.
It seems like Yamada lacks the sex appeal of an adult.
What should we do?
I thought she might get depressed like this.
It's so sad that I can't bear to look at her.
What should we do?
Hmm...
Todoroki-san.
Souma-kun.
If you just work like normal, the time till the manager comes back won't seem to go as slowly.
You think so?
And if that's not enough to distract you, you could try serving Satou-kun instead.
Oh, I see.
Can I serve you?
Hey, did your loneliness cause your brain to short-circuit?
Satou-kun, is there anything I can help you with?
How about food?
Are your buttons loose?
Would you like a parfait?
No.
Satou-kun, are you tired?
What's wrong?
I wonder...
Actually, Satou-kun...
I have just one little favor to ask of you.
What is it?
Since we're in this situation...
could you call me Yachiyo?
Satou-kun! Satou-kun, are you all right?
Wh-Why does it come to this?
Um, uh, it's a matter of feelings.
Also, Kyouko-san calls me Yachiyo.
So, then... I'll...
Instead of Satou-kun, I'll call you Jun-kun!
If you're going to choke, you should stop smoking.
I'm sorry. My asthma always acts up when someone calls me by my first name.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
Um, I don't really like being called Todoroki.
It sounds really manly.
Well, I understand that.
I'm so happy.
It's always been a dream of mine to have a friend my age call me by my first name.
By a friend...
You're...
...not doing this on purpose, are you?
Right then, let's head home.
O-Okay...
If you're going to be that far away, it's no different from when we're at work.
But I can't just do it all of a sudden.
Then, do you want to review some classic literature to distract yourself?
I'll quiz you.
Oh, okay.
Here, Inami-san.
Practice for holding hands.
All right.
This is the best I can do right now.
But I feel pathetic for feeling relieved.
I'm so tired from cram school.
So, in what instances is the word "Otsu" used?
Um...
Oh.
It's Onii-chan. Is he on his way home from work?
Onii...
Could that be... Onii-chan's girlfriend?
But what's that?
I'm curious.
Todoroki. I'm fine here so go out to the floor.
Todoroki?
Yachi—
I'm back!
Kyouko-san! Isn't it a little early for you to be back?
I met Otoo there, so I let him take care of the rest.
Satou-kun, Kyouko-san is back!
So I see...
Welcome back.
Yachiyo, did something happen between you two?
Huh? Oh, yes!
We deepened our friendship.
I've never had a friend the same age as me, but Satou-kun is a really great friend.
It felt like he was thirsty for my blood.
Huh?
Never mind.
Oh, right. Yachiyo.
There's someone I want you to take care of today.
Eh? Um, is it a new employee?
Something like that.
Hello.
Well, I'm Takanashi Nazuna.
Nice to meet you.
Nazuna?
Who is this?
It's Katanashi-kun's little sister.
Why are you here?
I have a workplace experience assignment, so I asked the manager.
By experiencing work, one can learn independence as well as one's responsibilities as a member of society.
Education is brilliant!
Offering
What are you holding?
I'll work hard today.
This is the girl I saw yesterday.
I'm Takanashi Nazuna.
Nice to meet you.
Um, I'm Inami Mahiru.
Yes.
She seems so quiet and lady-like.
I can't let her see me hitting her brother.
All right!
I won't hit him all day today!
I'll do my best!
I bet that's what she's thinking.
But who knows how long that'll last.
Nazuna-chan! Is it true you're really an elementary school student?!
Yes.
I-I wonder why she's staring at me so much.
Inami-san.
Huh? Y-Yes?
You were walking with my brother yesterday, right?
U-Um...
You don't have to get so flustered.
It's not like you were doing anything inappropriate.
Inappropriate?
Hits him a lot
I'm not doing anything like that.
I'm sorry.
Huh?
Oh, I've got to clean up the cup I broke.
I was wondering what kind of girl Onii-chan would get close to, but she seems like a normal, quiet girl.
Kind of a let-down.
Oh well.
I'll just wrap Inami-san around my little finger, like my sisters.
I'm sorry!
Onii-chan! Why?
Why did you get hit?
It's okay.
This always happens.
Always happens?!
Nazuna, how do I explain...
Society has lots of different kinds of people.
Society?!
I'm sorry!
Thank you very much.
Katanashi-kun, do you know where's Nazuna-chan?
Yes, I told her to hang out with Inami-san who's on her break.
Then, Yamada will also go on her break.
You still have work to do.
Here's some tea.
Go ahead.
Stare
Scary.
Why doesn't Onii-chan get mad when he gets hit?
Actually, why were they walking home together?
Um, Inami-san?
Y-Yes?
It's about my brother...
Um...
Does Onii-chan... like getting hit?
Does... Onii-chan... like...?
Do you... like Onii-chan?
Um...
Please answer me honestly!
I just want to know.
I'm not going to do anything about it.
It's true.
Really?!
It's true!
I see.
So Onii-chan really is...
one of those masochistic people.
Inami-san.
Yes?
Please take care of my brother.
Huh? What?!
Nazuna-chan sure is relaxed for her first time.
Well, I'm sure she'd be fine even with a difficult customer.
She's really responsible like that.
Yamada can do it too.
Oh? So you're able to work the cash register now?
Future Yamada is able to.
But I asked the present Yamada.
Thank you for today.
It's a shame you're leaving so soon.
You learned the job quickly, and the uniform looked great on you.
It's all right! Starting tomorrow, Yamada will do her best!
I'll expect you to do great work starting tomorrow then.
She doesn't trust me.
Onii-chan.
What is it?
No matter what kind of person you are, you'll always be my Onii-chan!
Um, okay.
See ya.
Um... I'm sorry for everything,
like hitting you in front of Nazuna-chan.
Oh. No, it's fine.
I can endure it until your illness is cured.
Huh?
Once your androphobia is cured, we can wave goodbye to things like this.
U-Um... But...
What? Goodbye?
Let's do our best.
Agitation
Why?!
I see. Now that I think about it...
Once my androphobia is cured, Takanashi-kun won't hang out with me anymore.
B-But I need to cure my androphobia. I really want to!
Besides, if I don't cure it, Takanashi-kun will be disappointed.
Geez, what should I do?!
For the time being... let go of me.
I'm sorry.
Jeez, I told you I'd be with you.
Huh?
Also, I don't think that your androphobia will be cured anytime soon.
So you can just act like you always have.
Takanashi-kun...
Let's take our time and continue to work hard together.
Just make sure you're not set to "lethal."
I-I'll do my best!
Okay, let's get back to work.
So you can just act like you always have.
Omoidoori nya susumanai
I can’t get as far as I’d like
Koi ni daiji na Communicate
In love, communication is most important
Donna kotoba ga meichuu
What kinds of words would hit the mark?
Kokugo jiten wo mekurou
I’ll flip through a Japanese dictionary
Omomurou ni towazugatari de atsui kimochi wo tsugemashou
Slowly and without warning, I’ll convey these passionate feelings to you
Saredo ingin na kono mune wa jouzetsu ni wa narenai
Or so I thought, as my bashful heart is nowhere near confident enough
Monooto ni Delicate desu mamoru mi no sube shirimasen
I’m delicate to sounds. I don’t even know how to protect myself
Dakedo tantou wa yaomote desu tsune ni genba shobu
But the one in charge takes the full brunt. It’s constantly a battlefield!
Kokoroiki wo takaraka ni jibun Mode de Try shiyou
I’ll louden my disposition and try again in ‘myself’ mode
Heart no Edge ni idomou
I’ll challenge at the edge of my heart
Omou dake mitsumete moshikashitara to At Random
And gaze fixedly at only my feelings. It might come anytime at random
Chance wo matte mirubeki
So it’s best to wait for your chance!
Heart no Ace wo mekurou
I’ll flip over the ace of my heart
Nenriki de mitsumete ai no katachi no Silhouette
And gaze fixedly on my willpower. I’ll search for the image
Image wo saguri dasou
Of the shape of love’s image
Nerai doori ni susumitai
I want to get to where I’m aiming for!
Neko no senaka wo mane shitai
I want to be like the back of a cat
Although my androphobia is an issue,
we also need to cure your disorder, don't you think?
I'm not crazy or anything.
Between an idol and a water flea, which one do you think is cuter?
A water flea.
He's crazy.
Even comparing the two is an insult to water fleas!
This is what he's like.
I like this weirdo who looks like he'll never be loved.
Am I going to be okay?
Wait a second.
That means...
not many others will be interested in him, so I should be relieved?
You weirdo!
Next episode preview
Next episode preview:
Good work, Takanashi-kun.
Good work to you too.
Now that I think about it, Chief and Satou-san have been working together for a while now.
Yeah, Satou-kun was so cute back then.
Cute?
Next time, Yachiyo and Satou back then.
And, welcome to the Takanashi household.
Next: Item 11
Yachiyo and Satou Back Then. And, Welcome to the Takanashi Household.
Also, he was kind of a delinquent.