I’m gonna spend today with Kyouko-san.
Good morning.
What’s going on?
What is everyone doing over there?
Katanashi-kun!
Well, you see, there was a woman collapsed right outside the store.
Looks like a drunk.
A drunk? Collapsed?
Yeah.
Souta!
Huh? Do you know her?
N-No! I mean... She’s just a woman who lives in my neighborhood!
I got dumped again!
As you can see, she has some issues with drinking.
I’ll take care of this, so everyone, please get back to work.
Go on, hurry now.
I need to make Kyouko-san her parfait....
Why are you here?
My boyfriend dumped me so I was sad, lonely, and got bored.
I was hoping you would comfort me, Souta.
Go home, Kozue-neesan.
That person is your sister?
Yeah, you see—
Why are you standing there, Inami-san?!
I was just changing.
I’m Souta’s older sister, Takanashi Kozue.
Hey, be quiet!
Ow!
Is my younger brother causing any problems?
If that’s the case, feel free to hit him.
By the way, I teach a self-defense course for women.
If you’d like, why don’t you join?
No, thank you.
Hurry up and go home!
You’re so cold, Souta.
To think, you were this cute when you were younger.
W-Wait, stop it, Kozue-neesan!
What a cute little girl!
Right? That’s Souta.
Our mother was very frugal; probably a result of having a lot of children.
Clothes and toys were all hand-me-downs from older sisters, and Souta was no exception.
Isn’t Souta cute?
Inami-san.
Y-Yes?!
Oh Souta, when did you...?
Can you please keep this a secret from everyone else?
About my sister, and this photograph?
Please!
O-Okay.
As you may already know,
since Inami-san has a severe case of androphobia,
she, at times, takes excessive self-defensive action.
No!
I-I’m sorry!
Wow, you’re pretty strong!
D-Don’t praise her for that...
Item 4
Souma, a fresh... too fresh, youth.
Dammit, thanks to Kozue-neesan I got hit again.
I’ve already destroyed the photo, and Inami-san promised she’d keep quiet about it,
so I guess I’m safe for the moment.
Souma, are you done yet?
I’m about to serve this one.
Hey, Satou-kun,
I think this salad has a bit less lettuce than usual.
It’s fine, stop being so picky and hurry it up.
Souma-san...
Now that I think about it, I haven’t talked to him that much.
You’re annoying.
That hurt, Satou-kun.
Rather than picky, maybe he’s just an observant person.
Oh, so something like that happened?
Yeah. So, what kind of person is Souma-san?
He’s a good person.
Man, I got yelled at by Satou-kun again today.
Oh, Souma-san.
Seems like I’m so slow on the job that I’m kinda useless.
That’s not true, it’s just that you’re very methodical.
Thanks.
Huh? Taneshima-san, did you happen to get taller?
Really? You can tell?!
Yep.
About 1 millimeter.
Ah, that’s great!
1 millimeter?
You’ve been drinking milk every day, right?
Yeah!
Also, you’ve been hanging upside-down on the monkey bars,
and trying just about anything to become taller!
At this rate, you won’t even need to wear platform shoes anymore.
S-Souma-san!
What is it?
I’ll go throw out the trash for you, so don’t say anymore.
Thanks, Taneshima-san!
What’s wrong, Takanashi-kun?
N-Nothing...
You sure seem to know a lot.
That’s not true.
Souma-kun, you can’t let other people do your work.
How could you let Poplar-chan take out that heavy trash?
That wasn’t my intention...
Speaking of throwing out the trash, Todoroki-san...
What is it?
It would probably be a good idea to stop leaving people there after ambushing them in the park.
Chief, did you...?
N-No, you’re mistaken...
They may have been customers who were after the manager,
but it’s still best to avoid being caught.
I’m sure there are other...
S-Souma-kun, I’ll do the food inventory for you!
Todoroki-san is so nice.
This guy... does he know my secrets as well?
Oh, Takanashi-kun.
Was your sister all right?
It seems that she passed out in front of the store today.
He knows!
Things seem rather complicated for you too.
You have two other older sisters;
one who’s a lawyer and the other a novelist.
Oh, and you also have a younger sister who’s in elementary school, right?
How do you know so much?
And this is a picture of you as a child.
But I threw it away! How do you have it?!
You sure are cute there. I was so surprised!
Please don’t put it back in your pocket!
At first I was so worried about whether I’d become friends with you, but now I’m relieved.
S-Souma-san?
Don’t worry; it’s really nothing. I won’t tell anyone.
However, if I’m in a pinch, I might use it as a bargaining chip.
Bargaining chip?!
Souma-san, I’ll do the dishes for you.
But...
Don’t worry, I’m free anyway.
Takanashi-kun, such a nice person.
Hey Souma, don’t get too carried away.
Today, Kyouko-san said she liked my parfait...
He’s listening to stories about how great Kyouko-san is...
Satou-san likes the chief, right?
But the chief likes the manager...
Just watching this wears me out.
You too?
You scared me!
What is it all of a sudden?
Don’t you want to do something for him?
Souma-san, you know?
There’s not much I don’t know.
We should avoid doing anything unnecessary though.
Really?
It seems like something could be done.
How?
I’ll just use a certain secret I know about
Todoroki-san, and persuade her to date Satou-kun.
What do you think?
No matter how you look at it, that’s just plain wrong,
and please don’t say that with such a cheerful face!
Looks like it’s over.
Hey, Todoroki-san, do you have a second?
Wait a minute, Souma-san.
I know.
What is it, Souma-kun?
I know you like the manager,
but I think it would be all right if you look at other people too.
Well, if it’s only that much...
Like for example, Satou-kun, or Satou-kun, or Satou-kun.
Souma-san!
Is something wrong with Satou-kun?
No, it’s nothing. Really.
Satou-kun...
He made porridge for me when I was sick.
I ended up giving it to Kyouko-san, though.
Also, he always listens to my stories about Kyouko-san.
But it seems as though he doesn’t like to see me around Kyouko-san.
Could it be?!
Looks like things are getting interesting, huh?
Please don’t get so excited.
Satou-kun!
What is it?
Um, saying something like this out of nowhere might be pretty embarrassing if I’m wrong, but...
Could it be that you...
l-like Kyouko-san?!
This took a wrong turn somewhere!
If that’s true...
I... I...!
Don’t draw your katana!
Todoroki, you’re...
an idiot!
Y-Yes... quite possibly.
My head hurts.
I’m done, so I’m going to go home and sleep. Good work.
Good work...
Takanashi-kun, Souma-kun, Satou-kun was really scary.
Satou-kun is such a nice person.
Yeah, probably the nicest one in this restaurant.
Order up!
Okay!
Um, Satou-kun?
What is it?
Did I make you feel uncomfortable before when I was saying those strange things?
It’s nothing, don’t worry about it.
Really?
Yes, really.
The food is getting cold, so hurry up and serve it.
I’m glad.
Souma-kun has said this before, but you really are a nice guy.
A while back, he told me that I should look at you more often.
I’m so stupid sometimes.
I’ll think about you more from now on. Definitely.
I’ll try hard!
Good for you, Satou-kun.
Th-That hurts, Satou-kun!
They’re at it again.
Good work everyone!
Huh?
This is unusual. Are you guys studying here?
Yeah, Inami-chan has a test coming up, so I’m helping her.
Must be tough.
Huh, Senpai?
What?
You look really cute with glasses on.
Really? Thanks. They aren’t real though.
It’s so cute when those big glasses slip down your nose.
What does that mean, Katanashi-kun?
Rather, even if you don’t have
glasses, you’re still small and cute.
Rather, you’re better smaller!
Rather, it’s best that you’re too small for your glasses!
I’m not that small!
Hm, classic literature and math.
I’m good at science and I can teach math fine, but I can’t do classic literature.
That’s because you don’t study on a regular basis.
I do! It’s just that classic literature and math are...
Classic literature and math are?
The teachers are male!
Even though it’s an all-girl school.
The best I can do is restrain myself from hitting them!
She’s living such a pitiful life.
I think I know this.
I like classic literature, so I’ve studied quite a bit ahead on my own.
But he’s one year below me!
You won’t learn by crying.
I’ll tutor you in classic literature.
You’re so nice, Katanashi-kun.
Not at all, it’s no big deal.
Besides, she’s been very helpful, lately.
So you
don’t spread
that information
around.
So it’s no big deal at all.
I see, it’s a bribe.
Japanese
Biology
Math
Classics
Inami-chan, you’re amazing!
You do just fine in other subjects.
I’m impressed!
Nice job getting passing grades in
Classical Literature and Mathematics.
Thanks to you two, I did even better in those than in my other classes...
Even though I got help from someone a grade below me...
So what’s with that look of dissatisfaction on your face?
A certain Sunday
It’s Sunday, but I still have work.
Before that, I have to get breakfast ready.
Good morning, Souta.
Good morning, Kozue-neesan.
3rd Sister
Takanashi Kozue (25)
Hangover... I feel terrible...
It’s because you drank an idiotic amount again.
You’ll be fine if you drink some water or milk.
Gotta count on alcohol for a hangover!
Is it a hangover or withdrawal?!
Go take a bath or something, and get rid of the alcohol!
Souta, can you wash my back for me?
Shut up, you drunk!
Geez.
Oh yeah, didn’t Izumi-neesan tell me to wake her up today?
Izumi
In the middle
of a job
Izumi
In the middle
of a job
Izumi
In the middle
of a job
Izumi
In the middle
of a job
Izumi
In the middle
of a job
Izumi
In the middle
of a job
Izumi
In the middle
of a job
Izumi
In the middle
of a job
Izumi
In the middle
of a job
Izumi
In the middle
of a job
Izumi
In the middle
of a job
Izumi
In the middle
of a job
Izumi
In the middle
of a job
Izumi
In the middle
of a job
Izumi
In the middle
of a job
Izumi
In the middle
of a job
Izumi
In the middle
of a job
Izumi
In the middle
of a job
Izumi
In the middle
of a job
Izumi
In the middle
of a job
Izumi
In the middle
of a job
Izumi
In the middle
of a job
Izumi
In the middle
of a job
Izumi
In the middle
of a job
Izumi
In the middle
of a job
Izumi
In the middle
of a job
Izumi
In the middle
of a job
Izumi
In the middle
of a job
Izumi
In the middle
of a job
Izumi
In the middle
of a job
Izumi
In the middle
of a job
Izumi
In the middle
of a job
Izumi
In the middle
of a job
Izumi
In the middle
of a job
Izumi
In the middle
of a job
Izumi
In the middle
of a job
Izumi
In the middle
of a job
Izumi
In the middle
of a job
Izumi
In the middle
of a job
Izumi
In the middle
of a job
Izumi
In the middle
of a job
Izumi
In the middle
of a job
Izumi
In the middle
of a job
Izumi
In the middle
of a job
Izumi
In the middle
of a job
Izumi
In the middle
of a job
Izumi
In the middle
of a job
Izumi
In the middle
of a job
Izumi-neesan, it’s morning.
Morning...? It’s already morning, huh?
2nd Sister
Takanashi Izumi (28)
Dirty room...
That’s strange... I just cleaned it yesterday.
That was me...
All these drafts are failures...
More importantly, your face is all black.
Go wash it.
I’m fine.
This is just the ink from my fountain pen.
I can’t use a computer.
You should just learn how to use one already.
It’s fine.
It doesn’t matter how dirty I become, as long as what I write is beautiful.
For I am a romance novelist.
You have no dream.
Also, washing my face is very tiring.
Just how exhausted is she?!
Eldest Sister
Takanashi Kazue (31)
Good morning, Souta.
G-Good morning...
Why are you scared?
Why are you carrying around
a lawbook this early in the morning?
Well, I am a lawyer.
Am I not allowed to carry it around?
Do you plan to infringe on my rights?
No, but you always end up throwing the book at me.
If you say that in public, I’ll get you charged for
calumny or defamation, and then sue you for slander!
Because the law is my weapon,
in many senses.
I think you mean in theory and in practice.
What did you say?
Kazue-oneechan.
Wasn’t your phone ringing?
Oh, really?
Yeah.
Were you all right back there, Onii-chan?
Since our sisters like to pick fights with you.
Yeah, you saved me.
I wonder why they only pick fights with you?
I wonder if it’s because you’re small.
You guys are just big.
About 172cm
About to
overtake him
About 172cm
About to
overtake him
About 172cm
About to
overtake him
About 172cm
About to
overtake him
About 172cm
About to
overtake him
About 172cm
About to
overtake him
About 172cm
About to
overtake him
About 172cm
About to
overtake him
About 172cm
About to
overtake him
About 172cm
About to
overtake him
About 172cm
About to
overtake him
About 172cm
About to
overtake him
About 172cm
About to
overtake him
About 172cm
About to
overtake him
About 172cm
About to
overtake him
About 172cm
About to
overtake him
About 172cm
About to
overtake him
About 172cm
About to
overtake him
About 172cm
About to
overtake him
About 172cm
About to
overtake him
About 172cm
About to
overtake him
And this is an elementary student.
About 172cm
About to
overtake him
About 172cm
About to
overtake him
About 172cm
About to
overtake him
About 172cm
About to
overtake him
About 172cm
About to
overtake him
About 172cm
About to
overtake him
About 172cm
About to
overtake him
About 172cm
About to
overtake him
About 172cm
About to
overtake him
About 172cm
About to
overtake him
About 172cm
About to
overtake him
About 172cm
About to
overtake him
About 172cm
About to
overtake him
About 172cm
About to
overtake him
About 172cm
About to
overtake him
About 172cm
About to
overtake him
About 172cm
About to
overtake him
About 172cm
About to
overtake him
About 172cm
About to
overtake him
About 172cm
About to
overtake him
About 172cm
About to
overtake him
About 172cm
About to
overtake him
About 172cm
About to
overtake him
About 172cm
About to
overtake him
About 172cm
About to
overtake him
About 172cm
About to
overtake him
About 172cm
About to
overtake him
About 172cm
About to
overtake him
About 172cm
About to
overtake him
About 172cm
About to
overtake him
About 172cm
About to
overtake him
About 172cm
About to
overtake him
About 172cm
About to
overtake him
About 172cm
About to
overtake him
About 172cm
About to
overtake him
About 172cm
About to
overtake him
About 172cm
About to
overtake him
About 172cm
About to
overtake him
About 172cm
About to
overtake him
About 172cm
About to
overtake him
About 172cm
About to
overtake him
About 172cm
About to
overtake him
About 172cm
About to
overtake him
Ever since dad died,
4th Sister
Takanashi Nazuna (12)
you’ve been the man of the house. Just keep at it, okay?
Nazuna...
You too. Since our sisters are like that, and mom’s never home, are you all right?
Yep. I’m totally fine.
For me, they’re all pretty easy to handle.
I love our sisters and you.
I-I see...
In many ways, I don’t think I can ever surpass my three elder sisters.
And Nazuna, my only ally, will undoubtedly become just like them in a few years.
I’ll go to work.
Good morning, Katanashi-kun!
It’s Sunday, but let’s work hard today, okay?
So small... So cute...
W-Why are you crying?
You look pretty bored, Souma-san.
Well, I was just chatting with the girls, and they all said they’d do my work for me.
I ended up not having anything to do.
He blackmailed them again.
Most of the men here are completely bossed around by the women,
but you seem unaffected, Souma-san.
Really?
It doesn’t seem like Inami-san would hit you, either. How nice.
Oh, speaking of which, it’s almost time for her to come in today.
Huh?
Inami-san is just a little...
You’re not good with her?
You and Satou-kun are pretty much the only guys she gets along with!
Wow, so there are some people you can’t deal with...
I see.
Eh? Why are you relieved?
You should just manipulate her with words like you do the rest of us.
You don’t think very highly of me, do you?
Anyway, she’s just beyond that.
Ah, Inami-san.
There’s no time to talk.
I guess she silences him before he even gets to talk.
Also, I don’t normally speak to someone unless I know a lot about them.
So basically, unless you find something you can use to blackmail them.
Inami-san always hits me or runs away; she doesn’t give me an opening at all.
Anyway, you should be fine as long as you stay in the kitchen.
You probably won’t even see her.
Souma-san!
I’m sorry, Souma-san!
I’ve thought this for a while now, but you really have terrible timing!
Are you okay, Souma-san?
I’m not okay.
It hurts.
My face hurts because she hit me.
Also my head hurts, and my heart hurts too.
I’m going to die. I’m going to die soon. I’m going to die right now.
Given that situation, you sure are talking a lot.
She’s been hitting me less since you started working here.
Since it’s me getting hit now, right?
And when she’s with you, she lowers her guard a little and it’s been a bit easier for me to get closer to her.
Really?
I hit somebody again. I’ve got to apologize.
Yeah, and as evidence of that, I recently
acquired the only info I have on Inami-san.
Remember when you complimented her hairpin?
Yeah, I remember that.
Well, ever since then, she’s worn a new hairpin every day.
S-Souma-san, stop it!
I didn’t... notice that.
I-I-It’s not what you think!
It’s really not.
It’s not like I was happy because a guy
complimented me for the first time in my life.
It’s just that I recently started collecting them!
Um, Inami-san...
And you know, I work better when I get complimented.
Please let go of Souma-san; he’s really going to die!
Ah, I’m so embarrassed!
Souma-san...
Souma-san, are you okay?
Um...
I don’t want to talk anymore.
He was silenced
Valentine’s Day
Takanashi.
Yes?
In American tradition...
Tradition? What is it all of a sudden?
In American tradition, Valentine’s Day is a day where the guys give something to the girls.
Give me some food.
Eat some beans from the Bean-Throwing Festival.
Here, Satou-kun, Souma-kun.
Thank you for always taking care of me.
Courtesy chocolate; like every year...
Thanks.
Thank you, Todoroki-san.
I’ve got to go give Kyouko-san some too.
Here, you can have mine.
Why? I don’t want it.
Even though it’s just a courtesy gift, I can’t accept it.
I’ll accept it properly when you return the favor.
Now you owe twice as much courtesy.
S-Satou-kun, frying pans hurt.
Frying pans hurt!
Um, Taneshima-san, to be honest...
A few days earlier
this is my first time giving chocolate to a guy.
Oh my, so it’s your first chocolate gifting.
Then how about you give these chocolates to Katanashi-kun?
What?!
He did help you study, after all.
The chocolate’s going to melt!
Katanashi-kun, here’s some Valentine’s chocolate for you.
We went together and worked really hard on picking it out.
Chocolate, huh?
That’s the case, s-so here.
All right, thank you very much.
I’ll work hard to return the courtesy.
A nosebleed before even eating the chocolate.
Inami-san, was that just the usual reaction?
Wait, that’s not it.
I didn’t hit you because I don’t like guys!
I was just hiding my embarrassment!
That’s even worse!
Omoidoori nya susumanai
I can’t get as far as I’d like
Koi ni daiji na Communicate
In love, communication is most important
Donna kotoba ga meichuu
What kinds of words would hit the mark?
Kokugo jiten wo mekurou
I’ll flip through a Japanese dictionary
Omomurou ni towazugatari de atsui kimochi wo tsugemashou
Slowly and without warning, I’ll convey these passionate feelings to you
Saredo ingin na kono mune wa jouzetsu ni wa narenai
Or so I thought, as my bashful heart is nowhere near confident enough
Monooto ni Delicate desu mamoru mi no sube shirimasen
I’m delicate to sounds. I don’t even know how to protect myself
Dakedo tantou wa yaomote desu tsune ni genba shobu
But the one in charge takes the full brunt. It’s constantly a battlefield!
Kokoroiki wo takaraka ni jibun Mode de Try shiyou
I’ll louden my disposition and try again in ‘myself’ mode
Heart no Edge ni idomou
I’ll challenge at the edge of my heart
Omou dake mitsumete moshikashitara to At Random
And gaze fixedly at only my feelings. It might come anytime at random
Chance wo matte mirubeki
So it’s best to wait for your chance!
Heart no Ace wo mekurou
I’ll flip over the ace of my heart
Nenriki de mitsumete ai no katachi no Silhouette
And gaze fixedly on my willpower. I’ll search for the image
Image wo saguri dasou
Of the shape of love’s image
Nerai doori ni susumitai
I want to get to where I’m aiming for!
Neko no senaka wo mane shitai
I want to be like the back of a cat
I was somehow able to accept
both Inami-san’s and Senpai’s chocolate.
Geez, that Inami-san...
It’s... kind of melted.
Why does he have two?
Next episode preview
Next episode preview:
There are a lot of male customers today.
Will you be okay, Inami-san?
Please don’t hit anyone.
I-I’ll be okay. I’ll endure it.
I can’t trust you.
What did you say?!
That’s why I can’t trust you!
Next: Item 5
On a certain sick day, it’s a different Wagnaria.
Next time: “On a certain sick day, it’s a different Wagnaria”.
I really am trying hard.