My name is Takanashi Souta.
I started working at the family restaurant Wagnaria,
where I’ve just had my first encounter with Inami-san, my androphobic co-worker.
Without even introducing herself,
she instinctively attacked and sent me flying.
As if that wasn’t enough,
my middle-aged manager had simply been careless in scheduling our shifts to overlap.
I won’t stand for this!
Please don’t make a mistake that could put my life in danger!
Well, you see,
Inami needs to get used to guys anyhow.
You know you just made a mistake!
Kyouko-san, that’s impossible.
Boys are... I mean... they’re violent!
You’re one to talk.
Well, that’s true, but...
You’re one to talk, too!
Anyway, how can Inami-san work here with that condition?
There are men working the kitchen, and male customers, right?
I’ve worked here a long time; I can do my work just fine!
Katanashi-kun... I wonder if he’ll be okay.
Ramen’s done.
Here, Inami, go serve it.
That’s a woman, that’s a woman, that’s a woman, that’s a woman...
Yeah, yeah, I’m a woman; I don’t really care. Just take care of it already, ’kay?
Is she okay?
Sorry for the wait.
I can’t do it!
Eh! My ramen...?
I couldn’t do it!
I was this close to hitting him!
It’s always like this...
So it is impossible.
Also, Satou-san, please stop talking like a girl.
Oh well, I’ll leave the rest to you.
In any case, I’ll serve the ramen.
She’s perfect with female customers, but as you can see, she has a difficult time with male customers.
She says that she’s at her limit just from trying to restrain herself from punching them.
Please don’t allow a dangerous person like her out amongst the customers.
She’s totally fine with the female customers, so isn’t it okay?
It’s not okay! Essentially, Inami-san is only half-qualified, right?
I-I don’t want to hear that from the new guy!
I’m a year older, and I know the work better than you do.
years old
Now, now, calm down, Inami-chan.
Even if that’s true, it’s meaningless if you can’t interact with the customers.
Inami, take this opportunity to use
Takanashi as a means to fix your androphobia.
What?
I’m not saying you have to like him,
but at least get to the point where you can work with him normally.
That’s right, Inami-chan.
Let’s do our best!
But...
Don’t I get any say?
Inami-chan, fight!
H-Huh?
And Takanashi, get over your issues with Inami so you can work with her—normally.
What?
I’ve been acting normal all along.
Though I’m not really interested in people over the age of 12, so I prefer to avoid dealing with them.
Oh, but Senpai, you’re an exception.
Why am I an exception?!
Well, since you’re so small and cute it’s okay that you’re older than 12.
I’m not small!
That’s enough. Just hurry up and cure her.
It’s not that I hate men, and I want to fix this too.
But I’m just so scared that I hit them on reflex, so I kind of feel bad for Takanashi-kun.
Men really aren’t that scary.
Takanashi-kun.
You’re definitely scarier, Inami-san.
Kyouko-san...
if it’s just from time to time, you can schedule me to work with Takanashi-kun.
You’re okay with it?
B-Because, Takanashi-kun...
pisses me off!
Katanashi-kun, pull yourself together!
Make sure you limit the skinship.
Do your best to become normal.
Yes!
I look forward to working with you, Takanashi-kun.
And I’ll be looking out for you, Inami-san.
This is why guys are...
This is why people over the age of 12 are...
These two will be okay, right?
Item 2
Inami, androphobia. That’s because I’m scared...
What’s up, Takanashi?
Already finish your shift?
Oh, no. I’m just thinking it’s almost time...
Huh?
Good morning, Takanashi-kun!
...for the hit-and-run waitress to appear.
I see.
Thank you for waiting.
Here’s your hamburger steak.
Here’s your cream soda. Sorry for the wait.
A boy!
Here’s your cheese gratin.
It’s quite hot, so please be careful.
Inami-san, you may only accomplish half your share of work, but you do ten times your share of violence.
It’s not my fault!
Inami-chan, you can’t keep hitting Katanashi-kun that much.
But... guys are so scary.
Katanashi-kun seems durable,
but hitting him so often is just too much.
But, even when simply greeting him,
I feel an urge to hit him.
Wait... Katanashi-kun?
Isn’t it Takanashi-kun?
Yeah, that’s right, Katanashi-kun.
Huh?
Huh... Perhaps I got his name wrong?
Takanashi
Katanashi
Takanashi Souta
Okay, I understand. I’ll do that from now on.
Right, I’m counting on you.
I always thought it was Takanashi, but Taneshima-san says it differently.
The characters are hard to read after all.
Um, is it Katanashi-kun?
Inami-san, it’s Takanashi.
Don’t get it wrong.
How dare you mistake somebody’s name!
It’s rude.
S-Sorry.
Katanashi-kun! Sorry, I tried to refill the coffee, but I couldn’t reach it. Can you do it for me?
Yes, Senpai!
It’s okay. I’ll do it later.
You’re terrible!
Inami-chan, what’s wrong?!
Why did I get punched this time?
Pisses me off...
Inami-chan...
How can I get Takanashi-kun to stop being so cold towards me?
Um...
I’m trying to be friendly with him, but what’s with that attitude?!
She was trying to be friendly...
Why do you think he’s like that, Taneshima-san?
Um, maybe it’s because you hit him?
But you’ve been greeting him properly and really doing your best, right?!
Yeah! I’ve been trying so hard to get along with him, even though I hate him, but he doesn’t even notice!
I get so nervous whenever I talk to him that I think,
“I was able to talk to him three times today,” or,
“I was able to go easy on him today.”
Day and night, I’m always thinking about Takanashi-kun!
I see...
It’s almost like she’s talking about someone she likes.
Takanashi-kun is always nice towards Taneshima-san.
Ah, um...
You know, the thing about
Katanashi-kun is that he likes small things.
Small things?
So probably, because I’m sma—
I’m not small!
Eh?
Anyways, Katanashi-kun likes things that are small.
Small things...
Now that I think about it, he did say something like that.
Something about a 12-year old.
Right, right.
I see!
So I just have to become a baby-faced, child-like, elementary school-looking person like you!
Taneshima-san! I-I didn’t mean it. I didn’t mean it, Taneshima-san.
No! You’re really not a child at all.
Look, you have much bigger breasts than I do!
I-Inami-chan...
Anyway, if I can adjust myself to his liking, I’ll have the advantage.
Advantage?!
If I become small, I can win against Takanashi-kun!
Inami-chan, what do you mean by ‘win’?
Become small...?
Is that even possible?
S-Sorry I couldn’t be of help.
It’s all right, I’ll never give up.
Somehow I’ll change myself to his
liking and make him warm up to me!
Going that far...
Inami-chan, by any chance, do you actually like Katanashi-kun?
Nope. I really hate him.
Tiny.
Now, now, Inami-chan. Let’s do our best, ’kay?
Those two... they should get back to work!
Todoroki, you should too. Don’t just look at them.
Matsumoto Maya
Yachiyo.
Yes, Kyouko-san?
Was there something I had to do?
Um... It’s about time for you to change our monthly goals.
Goals...
To be neat
and tidy
–Yachiyo
Current month's goal,
made by Yachiyo
What a pain.
Is actually
Kyouko's job
Yachiyo, I’ll leave it to you.
Yes!
So cool.
How so?
On break
Is that the new monthly goal?
That’s right.
To see
through our
customers' eyes.
–Yachiyo
You know how there can be something about a person that bothers those around them, but they don’t notice it themselves?
Yeah, there are things like that.
Aren’t there?
Indeed, I feel like there’s a perfect example right in front of me.
But this month’s goal seems pretty difficult.
Oh, I don’t think so.
Really?
For example, being unable to make eye contact with male customers,
or being so short that they simply can’t make proper eye contact.
Ka-Katanashi-kun, I’m not small!
I’ll do it! It’s a basic of customer service, right?!
Even if the customer’s a guy, I’ll make proper eye contact!
How?
B-By looking straight at the person, and directly...
Directly...?
...attacking.
Mahiru-chan, isn’t that a basic of martial arts?
Inami-chan, I’ll work hard. Let’s try our best together!
Taneshima-san.
Yachiyo-san, I’ll do my best too!
Popura-chan...
I’ll make myself taller even more often than usual!
To see
through our
customers' eyes.
–Yachiyo
Senpai, you’re so cute.
But... I might not be able to enter
the customers’ field of vision, even if I tip-toe.
It’s okay, the customers are usually sitting.
Um...
Eye contact is good, but... taking care of the customer is what’s most important.
Oh, right...
Well, that’s certainly true,
but do you think the manager can accomplish this goal?
Yachiyo...
To see
through our
customers' eyes.
–Yachiyo
Well, it’s probably impossible.
There!
On break again
Oh? So you ended up changing it?
Yes, I’m confident about this one.
Now, I have to go make Kyouko-san’s parfait.
Men's changing room
To see through our manager's eyes.
–Yachiyo
This will become a terrible place with a goal like that...
To see through our manager's eyes.
–Yachiyo
Takanashi, what’s that?
Ah, she’s a customer’s child.
You’re waiting for your mother to get out of the restroom, right?
Yeah.
Takanashi, I feel uneasy when I see you with a child.
How rude...
What is it?
I wanna be a waitress, too!
Really? I see.
But you have to wait until you’re a little older.
But that girl over there’s doing it even though she’s so small.
Hm?
You’re right! Isn’t it mysterious?
Katanashi-kun!
Explain it to her! Tell her that I’m 17!
Onii-chan, bye bye!
Thank you very much.
Kids are so cute.
Katanashi-kun really does like kids...
To think that she’s going to get older and grow up—it makes me sick.
...to a degree that worries me.
Mahiru-chan.
Yes?
Can you collect the dishes from table 23?
T-Table 23, that’s a male customer...
Sorry, but we have to clear away the dishes so that we can serve coffee.
Then, how about I clean up the customer first?
Mahiru-chan...
...I believe in you.
Oh, and be sure you ask beforehand if you can do it.
Yachiyo-sa—
E-Excuse me...
Um... uh...
I-Is it all right if I hit you?
It’s not all right!
I couldn’t do it, after all...
What are you doing?
That was close.
You can’t offer to hit a customer.
I know... so I just thought of a plan.
A plan?
I’ll control my urge to hit male customers until I reach my limit, and then...
I’ll just hit you instead.
This way, we can minimize the damage to customers!
Wh-What do you think?
What about the damage to me?
Eh?
I apologize for that incident earlier.
Huh? Ah... yes...
I’m truly sorry.
See?
The Chief is covering for your mistake.
If there’s anything troubling you, please let us know.
I’m sorry, Yachiyo-san.
Speaking of which, isn’t the manager supposed to do things like that?
Huh?
You mean how Yachiyo’s apologizing for Inami almost hitting a customer?
What else would I mean?
I hit anybody annoying, regardless of their sex. Is that bad?
If you’re like that, customers won’t come anymore.
It’s okay.
Where does that confidence come from?
If sales go down, I can just ask my useful juniors to bring in some customers.
The customers that just left; take all the money they have on them.
That’s dangerous. I’ve got to make sure we keep our sales up.
I’m so sorry that you had to apologize for me, Yachiyo-san.
It’s okay, Mahiru-chan. I’m just glad you didn’t hit him.
Yachiyo, I want to eat a parfait.
Yes, I’ll make it right away!
This restaurant... is it really going to be okay like this?
Takanashi.
Yes! What is it, Satou-san?
Good luck.
Which means he wants me to handle it, huh?
Katanashi-kun, good work today.
Same to you too, Senpai.
Today was a rather busy, wasn’t it?
You’re right. It was surprisingly busy.
I can’t believe customers come to this dangerous family restaurant.
Even we have our share of regulars.
I would never come to this place.
Really?
Oh yeah, earlier, a regular told me...
Told you what?
“You know,
one can become addicted to danger.”
Senpai, that’s not a good reputation for a family restaurant.
There’s no way this could become addictive!
Katanashi-kun!
I’m so sorry!
You alive, Takanashi?
Yachiyo, another parfait.
Coming right up!
I can’t get as far as I’d like
Omoidoori nya susumanai
In love, communication is most important
Koi ni daiji na Communicate
What kinds of words would hit the mark?
Donna kotoba ga meichuu
Kokugo jiten wo mekurou
I’ll flip through a Japanese dictionary
Slowly and without warning, I’ll convey these passionate feelings to you
Omomurou ni towazugatari de atsui kimochi wo tsugemashou
Or so I thought, as my bashful heart is nowhere near confident enough
Saredo ingin na kono mune wa jouzetsu ni wa narenai
I’m delicate to sounds. I don’t even know how to protect myself
Monooto ni Delicate desu mamoru mi no sube shirimasen
But the one in charge takes the full brunt. It’s constantly a battlefield!
Dakedo tantou wa yaomote desu tsune ni genba shobu
I’ll louden my disposition and try again in ‘myself’ mode
Kokoroiki wo takaraka ni jibun Mode de Try shiyou
I’ll challenge at the edge of my heart
Heart no Edge ni idomou
And gaze fixedly at only my feelings. It might come anytime at random
Omou dake mitsumete moshikashitara to At Random
So it’s best to wait for your chance!
Chance wo matte mirubeki
I’ll flip over the ace of my heart
Heart no Ace wo mekurou
And gaze fixedly on my willpower. I’ll search for the image
Nenriki de mitsumete ai no katachi no Silhouette
Of the shape of love’s image
Image wo saguri dasou
I want to get to where I’m aiming for!
Nerai doori ni susumitai
I want to be like the back of a cat
Neko no senaka wo mane shitai
Hey, Katanashi-kun...
What is it, Senpai?
I know it’s tough being hit, but please don’t be so mean to Inami-chan.
Inami-chan has a strong sense of duty and she’s very nice.
I think he understands a little!
Senpai is so small and adorable.
I’m able to continue this job because Senpai is here.
All right.
If you say so, I’ll work hard at it.
Really? That’s great!
She’s so cute when she’s happy too.
Just complimenting her on something small will make Inami-chan happy.
Complimenting someone who’s not small...
My stomach hurts...
Is it that hard?!
But I’ll do my best for your sake, Senpai.
Um... Inami-san.
W-What is it?
Um... Eh...
I-It’s really cute the way...
that hairpin looks today.
That wasn’t nice at all.
That was definitely your fault!
Inami-chan, you see, Katanashi-kun said that
because he was trying to give you a compliment.
He didn’t mean anything bad by it.
I want the two of them to get along better, but at this rate it might be a little difficult.
He complimented me...
I was so surprised that I hit him.
Maybe... it’s pretty simple after all.
Next episode preview
Next episode preview:
Um, Senpai, about the Chief...
Yachiyo-san?
I wonder why she carries that around all the time.
That?
Yes, that. That thing!
What?
Senpai...
Next:         Item 3
Yachiyo, Kyouko, Satou... And the returning Otoo-san.
Next time, “Yachiyo, Kyouko, Satou... And the returning Otoo-san.”
Who’s that?
Whaaat?